Chapter 976: Seizing the Heart

Shi Zhanfeng seemed to have already anticipated this, and he remained still on the spot as he flipped a hand over to produce a golden ball before tossing it upward.

Bursts of mechanical clicking rang out from within the golden ball, immediately following which it released a burst of radiant golden light.

The burst of golden light vanished in a flash, and the golden ball had transformed into a golden cage that was several dozen feet in size around Shi Zhanfeng.

The winged puppet swooped down onto the cage, then flapped its four wings vigorously, releasing a flurry of feather-like blades of white light that rained down upon Shi Zhanfeng, slicing tiny rifts into the space in their path.

At the same time, the feline puppet sped over from the other side, and its womanly head opened its mouth to release a bolt of silver lightning.

The entire golden cage was instantly inundated by silver lightning, while the blades of light came crashing down upon it incessantly, but after the dust settled, the golden cage remained firmly intact.

Shi Zhanfeng was completely unharmed inside the cage, and he was holding the crystal ball ine one hand while dripping his own blood onto it from the gash on the palm of his other hand, seemingly trying to undo the seal.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and he was wondering if he should take the crystal ball from Shi Zhanfeng.

He could sense that the aura of the heart sealed inside the crystal ball was extremely formidable, indicating to him that i twas a treasure on par with the Weeping Blood Array, and on top of that, it definitely had some type of important connection to the body of the Devilish Lord.

Han Li didn't really care if Sha Xin successfully resurrected the Devilish Lord, but he suspected that this Devilish Lord perhaps had something to do with Daoist Xie, and it would be quite a pity for a treasure of this caliber to be taken by Shi Zhanfeng.

However, if he were to swoop in now, he would definitely be regarded as an opportunist, and it was very likely that he would incur the wrath of both E Kuai and Sha Xin, thereby putting him in grave peril.

Right at this moment, he noticed that Shi Chuankong's shoulder had suddenly twitched in an almost imperceptible manner.

He raised an eyebrow upon seeing this, then asked through voice transmission, "Are you alright, Brother Shi?"

Shi Chuankong's shoulder twitched once again, this time more clearly than before, and even Mistress Liu Hua's attention was drawn to him, but he didn't do or say anything and simply looked away again.

After waiting for a moment, Shi Chuankong's voice rang out in Han Li's mind.

"I'm fine, Brother Shi. Would you be able to do me a favor?"

"Hold on just a little longer. I'm going to wait for their battle to become a little more intense before I come in to save you," Han Li replied through voice transmission.

"No, there's no need to save me for now. Your top priority must be to take that heart from Shi Zhanfeng. You cannot allow him to devour it no matter what. Otherwise, the consequences will be catastrophic," Shi Zhanfeng communicated in an urgent manner.

"What exactly does that heart do, Brother Shi? Why is it that Shi Zhanfeng has gone so far to secure it?" Han Li asked.

"I don't know exactly what it does, all I know is that it's extremely important to Shi Zhanfeng. In fact, it could even be vital to helping him break through his Great Encompassment Stage bottleneck. If we allow him to devour it, then you and I may as well never return to the Holy Realm again," Shi Chuankong replied.

Han Li was just about to say something else when a burst of incredibly formidable bloodline power and life energy erupted out of the golden cage.

Shi Zhanfeng had already undone the crystal ball seal, and he was holding the beating heart in his hands with a fervent look in his eyes.

Sha Xin was furious to see this, and she wanted to seize the heart back from Shi Zhanfeng, but she was also worried about E Kuai taking the holy remains, so she was caught in two minds.

Taking advantage of her momentary distraction, E Kuai abruptly sped his way around the Arhat puppet, then launched both fists at the puppet's back with tremendous power.

The puppet's head immediately swiveled around at Sha Xin's behest, and it attempted to defend itself with its eight arms, but it was just a fraction of a second too slow to react.

The puppet was already riddled with wounds, and as soon as E Kuai's fist struck it on the waist, its body instantly exploded into two pieces.

Meanwhile, the two puppets under Xiao Zi's command were still attacking the golden cage with all their might, and the cage was about to give out soon, but ultimately, they weren't going to make it in time.

"I'll crush all of you after I've completed my rebirth," Shi Zhanfeng chortled with glee as he raised the heart to his own lips.

Right at this moment, a blurry figure shot forth like lightning from the other side of the lake of blood, raising up massive waves of blood behind them.

Before Shi Zhanfeng had a chance to react, the golden cage around him exploded into pieces, and even the two puppets under Xiao Zi's control were sent flying from the force of the cage's explosion.

Han Li shot out of a vast expanse of silver lightning before throwing a vicious punch that connected cleanly with Shi Zhanfeng's chest.

A burst of starpower instantly erupted out his fist to blow a massive hole straight through Shi Zhanfeng's chest, and he was sent flying directly upward before smashing against the ceiling above.

The ceiling of the underground space instantly exploded upon impact, following which Shi Zhanfeng's body came plummeting down alongside small avalanche of loose rocks.

A loud splash rang out on the lake of blood, and as Shi Zhanfeng slowly rose to his feet, he paid no heed to the hole in his own chest.

Instead, he stared at his own empty hands for a moment before letting loose a heart-wrenching roar of fury and indignation.

Meanwhile, Han Li was standing on the opposite shore of the blood lake, holding the beating heart in his hands with a contemplative look on his face.

Everyone was completely taken aback by this sudden turn of events, including Sha Xin.

However, E Kuai paid no heed to Han Li and Shi Zhanfeng at all, and he took advantage of Sha Xin's lapse in concentration to rush past her with extraordinary speed.

An alarmed look appeared on Sha Xin's face as she tried to stop him, but it was already too late, and E Kuai appeared beside the holy remains in a flash before grabbing down at it with a frenetic look in his eyes.

Right at this moment, a bone spear shot forth through the air, producing a sharp screeching sound as it struck E Kuai on the wrist. Once again, Kun Yu had temporarily foiled E Kuai's plans.

E Kuai was furious at Kun Yu's repeated interventions, and he gave the spear a vicious backhand swat.

The tip of the spear was instantly snapped, and it flew back at Kun Yu at an incredible speed, piercing through his chest and sending him flying before he had a chance to react.

After knocking Kun Yu away, E Kuai reached out for the holy remains once again.

Right at this moment, a radiant pillar of golden light descended out of the heavens, hurtling directly toward his head.

E Kuai harrumphed coldly as he threw a punch at the oncoming pillar of golden light while continuing to reach down with his other hand.

The pillar of golden light struck E Kuai's fist with a resounding boom, and ripples of golden light erupted in all directions.

E Kuai's entire body stiffened as his feet sank half a foot into the ground, and a surprised look appeared on his face.

Before he had a chance to steady himself, a golden tail that was around forty to fifty feet in length and as thick as a millstone swept out of the golden light before striking him on the body to send him flying.

The golden light in the air then faded away to reveal a golden dragon puppet that was roughly two hundred to three hundred feet in length.

The dragon's entire body looked as if it were crafted from gold, and it had a pair of coral-like horns on its head. The layer of golden scales over its body, its long and powerful tail, and its thick and menacing claws were all clear indications of its immense power.

At the same time, three more puppets appeared beside the holy remains, namely a golden tiger, a golden turtle, and a golden bird.

These auras of these three puppets weren't inferior to that of the golden dragon puppet in the slightest, and Sha Xin descended onto the back of the golden bird puppet, following which a series of translucent threads shot out of her fingertips before vanishing into the bodies of all four puppets.

Even though the hole in her chest had been sealed, she was still looking extremely pale, and blood was trickling down from the corner of her lips.

As for E Kuai, he had been caught off guard and sent flying over a thousand feet, but he was quickly able to stabilize himself, and he appeared to be completely unharmed.

The four puppets immediately positioned themselves between E Kuai and the holy remains at Sha Xin's behest.

"The Astral Four Symbol Puppets really are quite formidable. If you weren't injured, perhaps they would truly pose a threat to me, but given your current state, how much of their power will you actually be able to wield?" E Kuai sneered, then swooped down at the holy remains once again.

Chapter 977: Shi Zhanfeng’s Revenge

As E Kuai came swooping down from above, a giant black sword that was over ten feet in length appeared in his grasp amid a flash of black light. The sword was slightly curved, resembling a black dragon, and it was giving off an incredibly formidable aura.

A series of white patterns were engraved onto the blade of the sword, forming a starry cloud design with over two hundred star acupoints flashing within it.

A grim look appeared on Sha Xin's face at the sight of the sword, and the four puppets instantly converged toward E Kuai at her behest.

Despite how massive the sword was, it appeared to be no heavier than a feather in E Kuai's hands, and he swung it through the air at the four oncoming puppets.

A fierce battle ensued, and a string of resounding booms rang out, causing the entire entire underground space to tremble violently.

E Kuai was revealing the full extent of his power here, and it was truly an incredible sight to behold.

Just as he predicted, the injuries sustained by Sha Xin hampered her puppet manipulation prowess significantly, and she was quickly forced onto the back foot, but she was still able to prevent E Kuai from reaching the holy remains for now.

Han Li was standing beside the holy remains at the center of the lake of blood, observing the battle between Sha Xin and E Kuai with a stunned look in his eyes.

Even though he had opened over two hundred profound acupoints in the Weeping Blood Array, there was still a massive gap between himself and the two city lords.

"Give the heart back to me, you human scum!"

Right at this moment, a furious roar rang out as Shi Zhanfeng came rushing at Han Li with a near deranged look in his eyes.

The hole in his chest had already healed, and a series of black patterns had appeared over his arms, giving off an extremely cold and violent aura.

On top of that, his speed had also been greatly enhanced, and he reached Han Li in the blink of an eye before throwing an almighty punch.

A vast expanse of black light erupted out of the palm of his hand, forming a black fist projection that was several dozen feet in size.

Han Li threw a punch of his own to oppose the black fist projection, and a resounding boom rang out as the fist projection exploded upon contact.

An unnatural flush appeared over Shi Zhanfeng's face, and he was sent flying back through the air, but Han Li was also sent stumbling back three steps in succession as a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes.

That black fist projection had been imbued with far greater power than what Shi Zhanfeng had demonstrated up to this point, and it had also released bursts of strange, invasive power that were surging into his body, completely bypassing his True Extreme Film.

Right at this moment, the two puppets under Xiao Zi's control appeared above Shi Zhanfeng, and the winged puppet flapped its wings to send a flurry of blades of white light raining down upon Shi Zhanfeng, while the feline puppet opened its mouth to release what appeared to be around a dozen silver branches, each of which released a bolt of silver lightning that also crashed down upon Shi Zhanfeng.

A disdainful sneer appeared on Shi Zhanfeng's face as a translucent black film appeared over his entire body, withstanding the blades of white light and bolts of silver lightning with ease.

At the same time, he abruptly lashed out with both hands, and two giant blades of black light erupted out of his arms, sweeping through the air toward the two puppets.

An alarmed look appeared on Xiao Zi's face upon seeing this, but before she had a chance to do anything, the blades of black light had already struck her puppets.

In the face of the blades of black light, the two puppets were each sliced into two as easily as a hot knife gliding through butter.

Xiao Zi was astonished to see this, and Han Li was also rather taken aback.

Even though Sha Xin was still locked in battle against E Kuai, she had also been keeping an eye on the heart this entire time, and she called out in an urgent voice, "Xiao Zi, don't worry about Shi Zhanfeng, prioritize seizing the heart! Don't let it fall into the hands of that human!"

Xiao Zi turned to Han Li in a hesitant manner upon hearing this, but didn't immediately act.

A displeased look appeared in Sha Xin's eyes upon seeing this, and she quickly made a hand seal, upon which a series of golden patterns appeared over Xiao Zi's glabella.

A cold and emotionless look instantly appeared on her face as she swept her sleeves through the air, releasing a pair of golden balls that transformed into a pair of giant, golden humanoid puppets in the blink of an eye.

The puppets were clad in full suits of golden armor, and each of them was wielding a golden shield in one hand and a large golden sword in the other.

At the same time, they were giving off tremendous auras that weren't inferior by much even compared with Sha Xin's four symbol puppets.

"Please stop, Fellow Daoist Xiao Zi! I have no intention of claiming this heart for myself, nor do I wish to fight you!" Han Li hurriedly said.

However, his words fell upon deaf ears, and the two giant golden puppets launched themselves at him at Xiao Zi's behest, then swung their swords down upon his head with incredible power and speed.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he darted over a hundred feet away to the side, and the two puppets immediately turned and sped after him without any hesitation before lashing out with their swords once again.

At the same time, they were also using their shields as weapons, blocking all paths of escape and retreat.

To compound Han Li's woes even further, Shi Zhanfeng was also pouncing at him from another direction.

A burst of dense black light erupted out of the palm of his hand, forming a beastly black claw that was over a hundred feet in size, restricting Han Li's options even further.

A cold look appeared on Han Li's face as he tucked the heart down the front of his robe, then lashed out with his fists in all directions to unleash a wave of white fist projections.

The fist projections fanned out like the canopy of a peacock, and a string of resounding booms rang out as each puppet was struck by dozens of fist projections in an instant, sending them flying back through the air.

The black claw projection crashing down from above was also shattered by Han Li's fist projections, but Han Li's body also shuddered violently, and his complexion paled slightly as he took an involuntary step back.

Right at this moment, Shi Zhanfeng appeared behind him without any warning, displaying far superior speed to before.

At this moment, his entire body was enshrouded in a layer of black light, and he was wielding a black saber that he swung down at the back of Han Li's neck.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he suddenly fell forward, but his feet were still firmly rooted to the ground.

As a result, Shi Zhanfeng's saber flashed through the air above his head.

Shi Zhanfeng was clearly caught off guard by this, and he hurriedly tried to dart back in retreat, but right at this moment, Han Li's body sprang bolt upright again as he swung his right elbow at Shi Zhanfeng in a vicious strike.

The attack was too fast for Shi Zhanfeng to evade, so he could only raise an arm to defend himself. The black patterns on his arm lit up as it made contact with Han Li's elbow, and the clear sound of bones shattering rang out in his arm as he was sent flying back through the air with a stunned look in his eyes.

However, he then twisted around in mid-air before flying toward the pair of giant humanoid puppets.

At this point, the two puppets had already steadied themselves, and they paid no heed to the oncoming Shi Zhanfeng as they pounced at Han Li again while swinging their swords at him with formidable power.

Han Li was about to set off in pursuit of Shi Zhanfeng, but he was stopped in his tracks by the two puppets, and he lashed out with his fists in retaliation, unleashing a pair of huge, white fist projections that struck the oncoming golden swords with an explosive boom.

The two fist projections exploded upon contact, but the golden swords were also stopped cold in their tracks, while their puppet wielders were each forced back a step.

Right at this moment, a streak of golden light shot forth from between the two puppets, and it contained a golden spear that was aimed directly at Han Li's chest.

The wielder of the spear was none other than Xiao Zi, and at this moment, she was wearing a suit of tight-fitting golden armor that accentuated her gorgeous curves, and there was a design o fa majestic golden bird engraved onto the suit of armor.

The design was extremely lifelike, and every single line was radiating dazzling golden light, clearly indicating that this was no ordinary suit of armor.

Han Li joined his palms together to clamp the tip of the golden spear between them, instantly stopping the spear cold in its tracks.

A burst of radiant golden light instantly emerged over Xiao Zi's armor, and around fifty to sixty star acupoints appeared on its surface.

With her strength bolstered by the power transmitted into her body by the suit of golden armor, she tugged on her spear with all her might, but it remained firmly locked into place.

"Do you not recognize me, Fellow Daoist Xiao Zi?" Han Li asked through voice transmission as he looked directly into her eyes.

However, Xiao Zi was completely cold and responsive to his words, and a layer of crimson light appeared over her face beneath her veil, indicating that she was about to unleash some type of secret technique that granted her short-term power at the expense of severe long-term detrimental effects.

Han Li heaved an internal sigh upon seeing this, then thrust his palms forward, sending Xiao Zi and her spear flying.

Right at this moment, Shi Zhanfeng suddenly appeared behind Xiao Zi with a sinister grin on his face, and he swung his black saber down upon her head without any hesitation.

A black, beastly projection appeared over the blade of the saber, and its weight instantly increased by over tenfold as it swept through the air, leaving a long spatial rift in its wake.

Xiao Zi was still in the process of flying back through the air, so there was no way that she could evade the attack.

Chapter 978: Mission Completed

Han Li immediately sprang into action upon seeing this, and all 475 of his profound acupoints lit up as he launched himself forward with all his might, reaching Xiao Zi's side right before she was struck down before throwing a punch at Shi Zhanfeng's black saber.

However, right at this moment, the saber suddenly veered away to the side, avoiding Han Li's fist before sweeping toward his neck.

At the same time, the beastly projection around the saber let loose a low roar before pouncing at Han Li and biting down upon his head.

Han Li instantly felt a burst of tremendous pressure crashing down upon him, and even the light radiating from his profound acupoints had dimmed slightly.

He took a deep breath before lashing out at the black saber with his other fist, and simultaneously, a Giant Mountain Ape projection appeared behind him before pouncing at the beastly projection.

A resounding boom rang out as the entire underground cave shuddered violently, attracting the attention of even Sha Xin and E Kuai.

Golden, white, and black light intertwined, forming a three-colored ball of light, immediately following which Shi Zhanfeng shot back out of the ball of light before crashing into the nearby cave wall.

The black saber in his hand had been snapped into two, and the black patterns all over his body had become far dimmer than before. Blood was trickling down from the corner of his mouth, and there was a stunned look on his face as he hurriedly sped toward the entrance of the underground cave.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li also shot out of the three-colored ball of light with a furious look on his face, and he caught up to Shi Zhanfeng in the blink of an eye before throwing an almighty punch.

Radiant white light erupted out of his fist, resembling a blazing white sun, and all of the space within a radius of several hundred feet trembled violently as Han Li's fist rumbled through the air.

An alarmed look appeared on Shi Zhanfeng's face as bright starlight erupted over his entire body, and the black patterns on his skin also lit up to produce a black film of light.

At the same time, a gray shield flew out of his sleeve, and there were close to forty star acupoints glowing on its surface.

The shield instantly swelled to around ten times its original size, yet it had only just emerged before Han Li's fist came crashing down upon it, shattering it into pieces.

A fearful look appeared in Shi Zhanfeng's eyes, but before he could do anything else, a cold harrumph suddenly rang out, immediately following which he felt as if a red-hot poker had been plunged straight into his head, causing his entire body to stiffen involuntarily.

In that same instant, Han Li's fist struck him on the chest, and the black film of light around his body was only able to put up token resistance before it was also immediately overwhelmed.

Once again, Han Li's fist punched a huge hole into Shi Zhanfeng's chest, sending blood splattering in all directions.

Shi Zhanfeng's body was sent flying through the air, plummeting out of the sky like an asteroid before crashing down onto the ground near the entrance of the underground cave.

A resounding boom rang out as a massive crater was smashed into the ground, and a huge cloud of dust rose up into the air alongside countless pieces of debris.

Blood was gushing profusely out of Shi Zhanfeng's mouth and body, and it appeared as if Han Li's punch had almost torn his entire body apart at the seams.

The black patterns on his skin flashed momentarily before quickly fading away.

At this point, Shi Zhanfeng was on the verge of death, and he was staring up at Han Li with an incredulous look on his face.

Han Li was just about to descend upon him to deal the killing blow when a streak of white light suddenly shot forth from the entrance of the underground cave.

The streak of white light pierced through Shi Zhanfeng's head, revealing itself to be a white bone spear.

The light in Shi Zhanfeng's eyes quickly faded away, and everyone was stunned by this abrupt turn of events.

Sha Xin was looking on with a cold sneer on her lips, while a grim look had appeared on E Kuai's face.

With Shi Zhanfeng dead, Mistress Liu Hua was the only ally that he had left, and that was certainly far from ideal.

With that in mind, a hint of urgency welled up in his heart, and the light radiating from his profound acupoints instantly brightened significantly. At the same time, the black sword in his hand also began to glow radiantly as he swung it down upon the tiger puppet before him.

Sha Xin immediately pointed a finger in the tiger puppet's direction upon seeing this, and it instantly swelled drastically in size before opening its mouth to unleash a torrential barrage of blades of golden light.

The storm of golden blades swept toward E Kuai with astonishing might, but E Kuai merely harrumphed coldly as he swung his sword into the golden storm.

The barrage of golden blades was instantly sliced into two, and E Kuai's sword was slowed down slightly, but it was still able to strike the tiger puppet with immense power.

A resounding thump rang out as the tiger puppet was sent flying, creating an opening in the encirclement formed by the four puppets.

Sha Xin hurriedly spurred the other three puppets into action, attempting to close the opening that had just been created, but right at this moment, E Kuai swung his sword through the air once again, unleashing three giant, black sword projections that struck the other three puppets.

The three sword projections weren't as formidable as the attack that he had just unleashed upon the tiger puppet, but they were still enough to force each of the three puppets back a step.

E Kuai immediately pounced on this opportunity, darting forward as a white shadow to fly out of the broken encirclement, but right at this moment, a giant silver ape puppet that was around seventy to eighty feet tall barreled straight into him from the side.

E Kuai was clearly caught off guard by this, but he immediately reacted by swinging his sword through the air, instantly slicing the puppet into two.

However, this had bought Sha Xin enough time to rally her puppets, and the four symbol puppets sprang back into position to surround E Kuai once again.

A dragon's tail, a tiger's claw, and a golden beak shot swept forth from three different directions at an astonishing speed before striking E Kuai in unison.

E Kuai let loose a furious roar as he swung his sword through the air to defend himself, but he was still knocked back by the attacks.

Right at this moment, a figure sprang forth from the side before landing on the tiger puppet, and it was none other than Kun Yu.

There was still a gaping hole on his chest, but a metallic gleam could be seen flashing from the wound, and it wasn't bleeding at all.

"City Lord Sha, it's far too taxing for you to control the four symbol puppets on your own in your current state, so leave this tiger puppet to me," Kun Yu said.

Sha Xin nodded in response and conceded control over the tiger puppet to Kun Yu.

As for E Kuai, even though he had been knocked back, he remained unscathed, and he immediately sprang forward again after steadying himself.

However, with Kun Yu's help, the combat prowess of the four symbol puppets was significantly bolstered, and E Kuai found himself trapped among them once again.

......

On the other side, Shi Chuankong was still lying on the ground in a completely still manner, but he was looking at Shi Zhanfeng from afar with mixed emotions in his eyes.

Mistress Liu Hua's eyes lit up with elation at the sight of the white spear that had pierced through Shi Zhanfeng's head, while a burst of intense killing intent erupted out of Han Li's body as he yelled, "Who's there?"

Gu Qianxun emerged from the shadowy entrance of the underground cave as she chuckled, "Please don't exert such fierce killing intent upon a frail woman like myself, Fellow Daoist Li."

"How did you get here?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"I happened to stumble upon this place by chance," Gu Qianxun replied with a smile. "I have to thank you, Fellow Daoist Li. It's all thanks to you that I was able to complete my mission."

Han Li gave a cold harrumph, but didn't say anything further.

It was a good thing that Shi Zhanfeng had been killed by Gu Qianxun. After all, Shi Zhanfeng was the eldest prince of the Night Sun Empire, so killing him was sure to incur extremely severe consequences.

"Xun'er!" Mistress Liu Hua called out in an ecstatic manner as he hurried over to Gu Qianxun.

Han Li immediately jumped on this opportunity, appearing beside Shi Chuankong in the blink of an eye before thrusting a palm down onto his body.

"Stop!" Mistress Liu Hua yelled in an alarmed voice as he attempted to rush back to Shi Chuankong's side, but it was already too late.

The sound of something shattering rang out within Shi Chuankong's body, following which his mobility was restored, and he rose to his feet as he cupped his fist in a grateful salute toward Hna Li.

"You've saved me yet again, Fellow Daoist Li."

Mistress Liu Hua drew to a halt over a hundred feet away with a furious look on his face, but there was a snide gleam in his eyes, as if this was precisely the outcome that he wanted.

Han Li took a contemplative glance at Mistress Liu Hua, then turned back to look into the underground cave.

At this point, the three-colored ball of light had already faded away to reveal Xiao Zi, and she was currently standing on the spot with a dazed look on her face.

Right at this moment, the heart that Han Li had tucked down the front of his own robe suddenly flew out on its own, then sped directly toward Gu Qianxun.

Han Li hurriedly set off in pursuit, while Shi Chuankong followed along closely behind him.

An alarmed look appeared on Gu Qianxun's face at the sight of the oncoming heart, and she instinctively dodged to the side.

However, to everyone's surprise, the heart simply flew past Gu Qianxun before vanishing into Shi Zhanfeng's lifeless body in a flash.

Chapter 979: Daoist Xie's Former Owner

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

Could it be that Shi Zhanfeng wasn't actually dead? Could it be that he had been biding his time all along, waiting for an opportunity to seize the heart again?

With that in mind, an urgent look appeared on his face as he sped up even further, reaching Shi Zhanfeng's body in the blink of an eye before reaching out for his head with the intention of shattering it.

However, right at this moment, a burst of radiant crimson light erupted out of Shi Zhanfeng's body alongside a burst of tremendous force that sent Han Li and Shi Zhanfeng flying back through the air.

Han Li descended onto the ground over a hundred feet away with a wary look on his face.

However, contrary to his expectations, Shi Zhanfeng wasn't resurrected by the heart. Instead, his body began to rapidly shrivel up, and it was reduced to a dried up husk in the blink of an eye.

After that, the heart slowly flew out of Shi Zhanfeng's body, hovering around a foot above it while giving off radiant crimson light.

Han Li's eyes immediately lit up as he pounced at the heart once again, followed closely by Shi Chuankong, while Xiao Zi remained completely motionless.

"What are you doing, Xiao Zi?" Sha Xin yelled in a furious voice from afar.

Xiao Zi shuddered as she snapped back to her senses, and she was just about to control her two puppets to go after the heart when a pained look suddenly appeared in her eyes, and she threw her hands over her own head as she fell to the ground.

Han Li was able to secure the heart ahead of Shi Chuankong, following which he rushed over to Xiao Zi's side.

An agitated look appeared on Sha Xin's face as she hurriedly made a hand seal, and golden runes emerged from her fingertips.

A burst of golden light flashed over Xiao Zi's glabella, and an emotionless look returned to her face as she grabbed onto the golden spear beside her, then swept it through the air to send a wave of spear projections hurtling toward Han Li.

At the same time, the two giant humanoid puppets also came rushing at him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and right as he was about to retaliate, Daoist Xie's voice suddenly rang out in his mind, "That's enough! You two are on the same side, so you shouldn't be fighting among yourselves."

Han Li immediately drifted away to evade the wave of oncoming spear projections while also distancing himself from the two puppets, and the pair of puppets also stopped in their tracks.

Han Li turned his gaze to Xiao Zi and Sha Xin as he mulled over what Daoist Xie had just said.

Xiao Zi's expression remained cold and aloof, while Sha Xin was looking back at Han Li with a surprised look on her face.

After drifting back several hundred feet, Han Li said through voice transmission, "You've finally shown yourself, Brother Xie. Where are you right now?"

"I am inside the holy remains. Just now, my heart absorbed some very formidable bloodline power, and that's how I've been able to temporarily awaken, but I don't have much time, so listen carefully to what I have to say," Daoist Xie replied in an urgent manner.

Han Li had many questions that he wanted to ask, but he refrained from raising any of them.

"I can tell you now that my former owner is actually none other than myself. I was once the owner of the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but I fell prey to a plot hatched against me, and I sustained extremely severe injuries that left me on the brink of death. Hence, I had no choice but to refine this immortal puppet and seal part of my memories inside it.

“After that, some things happened, and this puppet descended into a lower realm, and that was where I first met you. It's all thanks to you that this puppet of mine was able to reach this place, and now, there is hope for me to resurrect myself.

“What you need to do now is fuse that puppet heart with my bonded core and my remains, and I'll be able to create a new physical body for myself using the tremendous bloodline power accumulated in this place over the course of countless years. During this process, I am not to be interrupted by anyone, so please protect me as I..."

Daoist Xie's voice became more and more faint as he spoke, and in the end, it trailed off into silence.

Han Li took a moment to process what he had just heard, following which began flying toward the holy remains at the center of the lake.

Shi Chuankong was looking at the heart in Han Li's hands, and he opened his mouth to say something, but could only muster up a forlorn sigh in the end.

Meanwhile, E Kuai had already noticed the bout of eye contact that had just taken place between Han Li and Sha Xin, and he hurriedly yelled in an urgent voice, "Stop him, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua!"

However, Mistress Liu Hua mere took an indifferent glance at E Kuai and didn't do anything.

E Kuai was furious to see this, and rays of crimson light began to emanate from his body, while his aura swelled drastically, indicating that he had just unleashed some type of secret technique.

Right as he was about to lash out with his giant sword, the two golden puppets under Xiao Zi's control suddenly pounced at him from behind while swinging their huge swords through the air.

E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly as he darted away to the side while swinging his sword at the pair of oncoming puppets.

The two puppets reacted very quickly, continuing to swing their swords at E Kuai while raising their shields to protect themselves.

Two resounding cracks rang out as their swords were instantly shattered by E Kuai's sword, following which the sword sliced deep into their bodies, but it wasn't able to slice all the way through.

Even though the two puppets had been severely damaged, they were still able to move, and they discarded their swords and shields in unison before grabbing onto E Kuai's sword with all their might, following which dazzling golden light began to radiate from their bodies.

An alarmed look appeared on E Kuai's face, and he hurriedly released the hilt of his sword before flying back in retreat.

Immediately thereafter, two earth-shattering explosions rang out as a pair of golden suns emerged, surrounded by countless spatial rifts.

The entire underground space trembled violently as countless loose rocks came tumbling down from above, plunging into the lake of blood to send huge waves sweeping over its surface.

At this point, E Kuai was already thousands of feet away from the epicenter of the explosion, and he was staring at the holy remains at the center of the lake with a look of fury and frustration on his face.

Right at this moment, the four symbol puppets converged to surround him, and Xiao Zi was seated atop the Xuanwu turtle puppet.

"Karma spares no one, E Kuai. For all of the crimes that you've committed, you're now all alone, and this is the day that you die," Sha Xin declared in a cold voice before raising a hand, upon which the four symbol puppets sprang into action in unison, sending all types of attacks raining down upon E Kuai.

Meanwhile, Han Li strode over to the holy remains, then carefully set the heart down into the skeleton's chest cavity.

The heart immediately began to glow with crimson light, as did the holy remains, and it was as if they were resonating with each other.

Han Li then pulled out that golden bead with a hesitant look on his face.

The heart naturally belonged in the body's chest cavity, but Daoist Xie hadn't specified where this bead was supposed to go. Was he supposed to put it in the body's dantian or its head?

Right at this moment, Mistress Liu Hua's voice rang out in his mind.

"I'm assuming that's the bonded core of the holy remains. If that's the case, then it should be fused as one with the heart."

Han Li took a glance at Mistress Liu Hua, and after a brief hesitation, he placed the bead onto the heart.

The bead immediately began to glow brightly before fusing with the heart in a flash, and the heart was instantly enveloped by dazzling golden light.

Within the span of just a few seconds, it had turned a bright golden color, and it had also swelled to several dozen times its original size so that it was proportionate to the massive body it was in.

The golden heart began beating far more vigorously than before, and a massive pillar of golden light erupted directly upward from the body.

The pillar of light was giving off tremendous aura fluctuations that caused the nearby space to tremble violently, and Han Li was forced back several steps by this enormous aura before steadying himself with a stunned look in his eyes.

The entire lake of blood began churning violently as it converged toward the body before flowing into the golden heart, and bursts of crimson light instantly erupted out of the heart before spreading to all parts of the body.

Countless bits of flesh began to appear over the surface of the remains before rapidly intertwining with each other, and the process was only being further sped along as more and more blood converged from the surrounding lake.

At this point, much of the ceiling of the underground cave had already collapsed from the battle taking place between E Kuai and the Puppet City cultivators, revealing the night sky above.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar tore through the night.

"Li Feiyu, I'm going to kill you!"

In the next instant, the entire lake of blood shuddered violently, and Han Li turned to discover E Kuai glowering at him with a look of murderous rage in his eyes.

In contrast, Sha Xin's eyes were bright with elation as she yelled, "Keep him contained at all costs! Don't allow him to interfere with Master's resurrection!"

Kun Yu and Xiao Zi gave a collective affirmative response, then began making a string of hand seals while changing an urgent incantation.

Among the four symbol puppets, the dragon puppet was prowling in the east while opening its mouth to release a blazing hot and highly corrosive breath.

The tiger puppet was situated in the west, and its mouth was wide open, releasing gusts of fierce wind that were as sharp as blades.

The Xuanwu turtle puppet was standing in the north, and a burst of azure light was surging out of its mouth, exerting mountainous pressure upon everything encompassed within it.

The Vermilion Bird puppet was hovering in the south with crimson flames flowing all over its entire body, and a jet of scorching fire was blasting out of its beak.

With Kun Yu and Xiao Zi's assistance, the four symbol puppets had become far more formidable than before, and E Kuai found himself trapped in the encirclement formed by the four puppets, unable to break free.

Chapter 980: Violet Spirit

There was a look of burning fury and urgency in E Kuai's eyes, and in the face of the relentless attacks from the four puppets, his skin had begun to take on a crimson hue.

All of a sudden, he let loose a thunderous roar before leaping up with all his might, trying to escape the encirclement by taking an aerial route.

However, as soon as he sprang up into the air, the pressure within the azure light surging out of the Xuanwu puppet's mouth increased significantly, and the fire blasting out of the Vermilion Bird puppet's beak also became far hotter and more fierce.

E Kuai's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, but he continued to rise up without pause, striving to break free from the encirclement so that he could prevent the resurrection of the holy remains.

However, right at this moment, Sha Xin swept a sleeve through the air, releasing a streak of golden light that transformed into an armored puppet with radiant golden lightning flashing all over its body.

The puppet was very strong and sturdy in appearance, and it was around ten feet tall. Its entire body was covered in golden armor, to the point that even its face was concealed behind a heavy visor. As opposed to any form of weapon, all it was holding was a giant golden shield that was over five feet tall.

As soon as the golden puppet appeared, it immediately sprang up into the air, then came plummeting down like a small mountain upon the ascending E Kuai.

"Get out of my way!" E Kuai roared as he threw a punch at the puppet, which responded by putting the entire weight of its body behind its shield.

A sound akin to a giant gong being struck rang out, and bursts of peculiar soundwaves erupted out of the shield.

Each successive burst of soundwaves was louder than the previous one, and they were like waves of the sea crashing against the shore with unfathomable power.

E Kuai felt a burst of overwhelming force radiate through his arm, and his entire body began trembling uncontrollably as he was involuntarily forced back down out of the air.

The shield-bearing puppet was also sent flying by the tremendous force of E Kuai's punch, tumbling end over end through the air.

However, right at this moment, a golden figure suddenly appeared within the encirclement formed by the four symbol puppets, and it quickly arrived by E Kuai's side, completely unaffected by the restrictive powers unleashed by the four puppets.

As soon as E Kuai landed on the ground, he immediately threw a punch at the golden figure, smashing a huge hole through the oncoming corrosive dragon's breath and blades of wind, but the golden figure evaded the attack with ease before abruptly appearing above E Kuai's head, revealing itself to be another golden puppet.

However, this one was far smaller than the shield-bearing puppet, standing at no more than three feet tall, and it was scantily clad in bits of golden armor that only concealed some of the sensitive regions of its body.

It was wielding a giant golden sword that was even longer than it was tall, and it pierced the sword directly down upon E Kuai's head.

E Kuai instantly swiveled around before throwing a punch upward, and a burst of radiant starlight erupted out of his fist.

In response, the golden puppet withdrew its sword before concealing its entire body behind it, using it as a shield. The force of E Kuai's punch was enough to send it flying into the distance, but at this point, the shield-bearing puppet had already made its return, taking over the responsibility of keeping E Kuai occupied.

The sword-wielding puppet sprang up into the air before landing on the shield-bearing puppet's shoulder, and the two of them formed a seamless partnership

"You're all going to pay for this!" E Kuai roared as he joined his index and middle fingers before pressing them against his own forehead, and a red flame-like symbol instantly appeared on his glabella.

"He's going to use a blood-incinerating secret technique! Brace yourselves, everyone!" Sha Xin hurriedly yelled in an alarmed manner.

Han Li reflexively wanted to enter the fray upon hearing this, but a hesitant look then appeared on his face as he turned back to the holy remains, which was still in the process of absorbing blood from the lake.

Right at this moment, a loud thump rang out around E Kuai, and all of his profound acupoints lit up, but they were glowing crimson rather than white. At the same time, his skin also took on a dark red coloration, and countless worm-like veins began to bulge over his body.

His aura was also rapidly elevating, and it was as if a cloak of blood mist had appeared around him, keeping out the restrictive powers exerted upon him by the four symbol puppets.

Immediately thereafter, he sprang up into the air, but before the four symbol puppets or the two golden puppets had a chance to stop him, he plummeted back down onto the ground on his own, adopting a horse stance as he did so.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as the entire underground space shuddered violently, and the ground around E Kuai began to disintegrate as countless giant rocks were flung through the air in all directions

In the blink of an eye, all of the giant rocks that had been flung up into the air within a radius of several thousand feet were reduced to tiny fragments, which continued to fly through the air as shrapnel.

The four symbol puppets had no time to take any evasive measures, and they were forced back by the tremendous force generated by E Kuai's stomp, while parts of their bodies began to implode one after another.

The sword-wielding golden puppet immediately hid itself behind the shield-bearing puppet, which was sent flying back through the air as it held its shield in front of itself.

Waves in excess of a hundred feet tall began to sweep over the surface of the lake of blood, sweeping toward the holy remains with immense power.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this, and all 475 of his profound acupoints lit up as he thrust both fists forward with all his might, unleashing a dense wall of fist projections that crashed through the oncoming waves of blood.

Moments later, the commotion subsided.

The entirety of the underground cave's ceiling had been destroyed, fully revealing the night sky above.

Han Li's fists remained clenched as he swept his gaze over the surrounding area. The four symbol puppets had already been completely decimated, while the two golden puppets were also nowhere to be seen.

Right at this moment, he suddenly spotted a delicate figure laying half-buried beneath the rubble. The black veil over her face had already fallen away, revealing her breathtakingly beautiful features, and sure enough, it was none other than Violet Spirit.

Han Li immediately rushed over to her side, then cleared away the rubble around her before lifting her up in his arms.

At this moment, Violet Spirit was in a state of unconsciousness, and her lower abdomen had been struck by a piece of rubble. Her brows were tightly furrowed in agony and blood was trickling down from the corner of her lips.

A pang of remorse speared through Han Li's heart at the sight of her terrible condition. If he had trusted his own instincts and identified her earlier, perhaps she wouldn't have had to experience this pain.

WIth that in mind, he sprang up into the air before descending onto the other side of the lake of blood.

From there, he made his way over to Mistress Liu Hua, then gently set down Violet Spirit, feeding her a pill as he requested, "Please look after her for me."

Mistress Liu Hua nodded in response with a grim look on his face, while Gu Qianxun was observing Violet Spirit with mixed emotions in her eyes.

Even though the restrictions in Shi Chuankong's body had already been undone, he was carrying some rather severe injuries, so he was unfit for battle.

After setting down Violet Spirit, Han Li sprang back to the other side of the lake.

Up ahead was a deep crater, at the bottom of which stood E Kuai. His skin had taken on a reddish-purple hue, and he was carrying Kun Yu by the throat as he made his way toward the lake of blood.

Kun Yu's dantian had already been completely destroyed, and he was as dead as dead could be.

"Everything has gone according to my plan, yet you've proven to be the only volatile factor. Ever since the Weeping Blood Array, you've been constantly foiling my plans. Honestly, I have a lot of appreciation for someone like you.

“If you hadn't resurrected the holy remains, I would've been tempted to take you as my disciple, but unfortunately, you also have to die today," E Kuai said as he casually tossed Kun Yu's body away, and it crashed into a distant cave wall before shattering into pieces.

"I'm truly honored that you think so highly of me, City Lord E," Han Li replied in a cold voice.

As soon as his voice trailed off, he channeled his Wingform Ascension Arts with all his might and abruptly vanished from the spot.

A cold sneer appeared on E Kuai's face upon seeing this, and he threw a punch in a certain direction.

Thanks to his blood-incinerating secret technique, his punches were imbued with astonishing power.

A resounding boom rang out, but as opposed to Han Li, E Kuai's fist had struck the shield-bearing golden puppet.

More specifically, his fist had struck the puppet's golden shield, and the surface of the shield immediately began to ripple like water, releasing bursts of compounding soundwaves that swept toward E Kuai.

The shield-bearing puppet was capable of using its foe's power against them, and as a result, it was able to counteract E Kuai's unfathomable power, resulting in a temporary impasse.

Chapter 981: It's Your Turn

At the same time, the sword-wielding golden puppet emerged from behind its shield-bearing counterpart like an agile golden monkey, springing up into the air before swinging its sword viciously down upon E Kuai's neck.

Its golden sword was riddled with star acupoints, and all of the starpower within it erupted forth at once, releasing a fiery aura that created a serrated edge around its blade.

However, as the golden sword came crashing down, the starpower erupting out of it clashed against the cloud of crimson mist around E Kuai's body, and sparks erupted in all directions as a screeching clang rang out.

The sword was unable to slice into the layer of crimson mist at all!

E Kuai gave a cold harrumph as he abruptly withdrew his fist from the golden shield, and as he thrust his fist forward again, the muscles on his right arm bulged, giving it an appearance of explosive power.

As E Kuai's fist struck the golden shield once again, the star acupoints on the latter flashed incessantly as it counteracted the force of his punch, but E Kuai simply ducked down to avoid the burst of reactive force, taking advantage of it to send the sword-wielding puppet flying.

At the same time, he struck the golden shield with his right fist a third time, and before it had a chance to reflect the force of his punch, he threw another almighty punch into the shield with his left fist.

A torrential barrage of punches came raining down upon the shield, and it was only able to withstand the ferocious assault for a few seconds before it exploded with an earth-shattering boom, while the puppet behind it was sent flying back through the air.

E Kuai was forced to take a few backward steps, and only after plunging his feet into the ground was he able to steady himself.

Right at this moment, Han Li descended upon him from above, and he was somehow completely unaffected by the shockwaves generated from the golden shield's explosion, as if he were a leaf drifting through a storm.

He channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts with all his might, and all of his 475 profound acupoints lit up as he threw a punch directly at the top of E Kuai's head.

His fist was enveloped in starpower, forming a radiant white first projection that was imbued with astonishing power.

E Kuai had been keeping an eye on Han Li this entire time, but he still didn't anticipate that Han Li would be able to strike at this moment. With no time to defend himself, he could sway his head to the side to withstand the punch with his own body.

As a result, Han Li's fist glanced past his head before crashing heavily down onto his shoulder.

The ground beneath E Kuai instantly exploded, sending countless shattered rocks flying in all directions, while E Kuai himself was tipped to one side and buried beneath the rubble.

Han Li continued to rain down more punches without pause, battering the ground over and over again to raise an enormous cloud of dust.

As the ground caved in over and over again, both Han Li and E Kuai quickly became hidden within the ever-deepening crater that Han Li was creating with his fists.

All of a sudden, a resounding boom rang out, and Han Li flew up from the crater before falling onto the ground outside.

Immediately thereafter, E Kuai came flying out in hot pursuit.

His entire body was riddled with wounds, and he appeared very bloody and battered, but in reality, all of these were only minor, skin-deep injuries. However, he was furious to have suffered the humiliation of being pummeled by Han Li like this.

After landing on the ground, E Kuai turned to Han Li as he sneered, "So you've also cultivated the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts. No wonder you were able to accomplish so much. Which statue do you have?"

At this point, Han Li had also identified that E Kuai was cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as well, and he was far more advanced in the cultivation art.

"Which statue do you have, City Lord E?" Han Li asked as he spat out a globule of blood.

"The Devilish Lord intentionally split up the four statues, and I've only managed to obtain two of them. Hence, you must have either the first one or the fourth one, either one of which will make a fine addition to my collection," E Kuai replied with a cold smile.

"How about we make an exchange?" Han Li suddenly proposed.

"Is this really the time to be making jokes, Fellow Daoist Li?" E Kuai chuckled.

Right at this moment, the ground beneath him abruptly shattered, and a golden figure shot out of the ground before grabbing onto him from behind.

The golden figure was none other than the shield-bearing puppet, which had just lost its shield, and a series of mechanical clicks rang out as its body split up into pieces before closing themselves over E Kuai like a golden sarcophagus.

The surface of the golden sarcophagus was riddled with profound runes, and at the same time, the sword-wielding puppet also sprang out of the ground.

It tossed its sword away before jumping onto the golden sarcophagus, following which its body also split up into pieces before fusing as one with the body of the shield-bearing puppet.

"Die, traitorous scum!"

A desperate roar rang out from afar, and it had come from Sha Xin.

Immediately thereafter, the runes on the bodies of the two golden puppets began to release blinding white light, following which both of them exploded violently.

A deafening boom rang out, and it was as if a radiant white sun had risen up in the night, completely illuminating the entire landscape.

Han Li had sprung back in retreat as soon as he saw the shield-bearing puppet emerge from the ground, and he was forced to shield his eyes from the blinding light and powerful shockwaves.

Some time later, the dust slowly settled, and Han Li saw a giant black crater up ahead.

E Kuai was standing at the bottom of the crater, and his clothes had disappeared, while his skin had turned pitch-black. However, it was a glossy black that was giving off a faint gleam, rather than a charred black that one would expect to see after such a powerful explosion.

Furthermore, the red symbol on his glabella had turned white.

A peal of harrowing laughter escaped E Kuai's lips, and all of a sudden, he vanished from the spot without a trace.

In the next instant, a loud boom rang out in the distance as Sha Xin's body was slammed high up into the sky.

E Kuai then immediately caught up to her before pounding her with a torrential barrage of punches, sending her tumbling down like a broken ragdoll, and it was unclear whether she was dead or alive.

He's become even faster and stronger!

A grim look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

"It's your turn now!" E Kuai said as he turned to Han Li, and even his voice had changed, striking the listener with a bone-chilling sense of foreboding.

In the next instant, Han Li's pupils abruptly contracted as he sprang back as quickly as he could, but E Kuai was still able to catch up to him in the blink of an eye.

His eyes were completely bloodshot, and it seemed that even his sanity had been a little compromised as he threw a punch at Han Li's chest.

In response, Han Li channeled both his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and his bloodline power, and his arms swelled up like a pair of balloons, forming a sturdy barricade in front of him.

At the same time, Han Li was struck by a very peculiar sensation, as if a type of special power had suddenly appeared in his arms, and it felt different from any previous occasion where he had separately channeled his true spirit bloodlines or the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

Before he had a chance to ponder this any further, a burst of devastating force crashed into his arms, and the bones in his arms were only just barely able to hold themselves together.

Immediately thereafter, he was sent flying back, leaving a massive trench that was tens of thousands of feet in length and close to a thousand feet wide in the ground, and he only drew to a halt after crashing into a rock face.

The entire rock face instantly collapsed, burying him under a huge pile of rubble.

Han Li's arms were feeling very numb, but thankfully, none of his bones were broken.

At this moment, E Kuai was burning through both his blood essence and his starpower, and the longer he used this secret technique, the more severe the backlash would be. Hence, his intention was naturally to end this battle as soon as possible, and he immediately launched himself at Han Li, refusing to give him any respite.

In the face of his almighty punches, the pile of rubble that Han Li was buried beneath was instantly reduced to dust, and a Giant Mountain Ape abruptly emerged before launching a massive golden fist directly at E Kuai.

E Kuai's entire body was dwarfed by the Giant Mountain Ape's fist, but he remained completely unfazed.

An earth-shattering boom rang out as his fist clashed against the giant oncoming fist, and a burst of tremendous power that surprised even Han Li himself swept directly toward E Kuai.

A stunned look appeared on E Kuai's face as he was forced back by Han Li's punch, but Han Li's entire arm was also in excruciating pain as he tumbled out of the air.

After landing on the ground, the Giant Mountain Ape abruptly transformed into a Lightning Bird, then flapped its wings vigorously as it flew away as quickly as it could.

"You're not getting away!" E Kuai roared.

Chapter 982: Borrowed Power

As soon as his voice trailed off, E Kuai sprang forward like a bolt of black lightning, appearing in front of Han as if by instantaneous teleportation before reaching out to grab his neck.

However, Han Li seemed to have already anticipated this, and he drew to an abrupt halt, stopping short of E Kuai's hand before darting back toward the lake of blood at a far faster speed than before.

As he drew close to the lake, Han Li reverted back to his human form with E Kuai in hot pursuit, and the latter sneered, "You sure have a lot of tricks up your sleeve!"

In response, Han Li advanced instead of retreating, channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts in conjunction with both his Giant Mountain Ape and Xuanwu bloodlines, and one of his arms abruptly swelled drastically in size.

A layer of coarse golden fur appeared over the arm, but pieces of azure bone armor had appeared over the back of its hand.

Han Li's fist was glowing with radiant starlight as it clashed against E Kuai's fist with an earth-shattering boom, and a burst of excruciating pain instantly speared through Han Li's arm, but he was only forced back a single step, while E Kuai was also forced back a step.

It was quite surprising even to Han Li himself that his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts could combine with his true spirit bloodlines to generate such incredible power, and for the first time, E Kuai was finally beginning to take his opponent seriously.

He took a step forward to arrive before Han Li in a wraith-like fashion, following which a layer of translucent light surfaced over his arm as he threw another punch at Han Li.

The punch appeared to be very light and lacking in power, but it was fast to the extreme.

Han Li was caught slightly off guard by this, and he could only channel his Xuanwu bloodline powers as he raised an arm to shield himself.

However, before the pieces of azure bone armor could even fully materialize on his arm, he was already sent flying by E Kuai's fist.

He flew over the lake of blood to the other side, raising massive waves in his wake before crashing heavily down onto the ground beside Violet Spirit.

Instead of continuing to go after Han Li, E Kuai made his way to the center of the lake of blood.

He looked at the body resting on the crystal slab at the center of the lake, and a series of emotions, including reminiscence, resentment, and indignation appeared in his eyes as he plunged his hand down upon the body's chest.

Right at this moment, all of the complex patterns on the crystal slab lit up in unison, releasing a burst of almost substantial crimson light that kept E Kuai's hand at bay.

At the same time, a resounding boom rang out from the other side of the lake of blood as Han Li launched himself at E Kuai once again.

He was channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and all of the true spirit bloodlines in his body with all his might, and all 475 of his profound acupoints were glowing radiantly.

A series of true spirit projections appeared behind him one after another, then vanished into his body again, and even though he didn't undergo any physical transformation, his aura had been significantly elevated.

Mistress Liu Hua was looking on with a hint of praise in his eyes, while Gu Qianxun and the others were also stunned by the power that Han Li was putting on display.

E Kuai had also noticed the change in Han Li's aura, and he immediately abandoned the holy remains before launching himself over ten thousand feet back in retreat, only to then immediately launch himself at Han Li again.

At the same time, it seemed like he had also activated some type of devilish bloodline, and a pair of horns emerged on his forehead, while his vertebrae began to protrude outward, piercing through his skin.

Simultaneously, his aura began to take on a more vicious quality, and the crimson mist that was emanating from his body had become very murky and was giving off a pungent, bloody odor.

He was slightly hunched-over as he charged at Han Li, and his speed had been enhanced even further.

All of the bystanders only caught a glimpse of a blurry afterimage before E Kuai and Han Li clashed, and the starpower and true spirit bloodline power that had converged toward Han Li's fist erupted in unison, crashing directly into the murky crimson mist around E Kuai.

The white starlight and crimson mist were whittling away at each other incessantly as two bursts of violent power erupted up into the air in unison.

Bursts of deafening rumbling rang out as countless spatial rifts were torn open in the air above.

Immediately thereafter, a thunderous roar rang out from the edge of the lake of blood, and all of a sudden, a burst of additional power erupted out of E Kuai's fist.

Han Li was already struggling to oppose E Kuai to begin with, and he was already tapping into as much of his power as possible with no more left to give. Hence, in the wake of this burst of power, he was instantly sent flying as blood came gushing out of his mouth.

A burst of crimson mist surged forward from E Kuai's fist, forming a giant fist projection that struck Han Li with tremendous power, launching him through the air like a cannonball that plunged directly to the bottom of the lake.

E Kuai descended out of the sky, crashing into the lake after Han Li before raining down punches in a torrential barrage.

The entire lake was trembling violently, and the blood level inside was rapidly falling, but Han Li was still nowhere to be seen.

A look of despair had appeared on Shi Chuankong's face, while Gu Qianxun had averted her eyes, unable to bear watching any longer.

Mistress Liu Hua also heaved a long sigh, and even Violet Spirit stirred slightly in her unconscious state.

......

At the bottom of the lake, Han Li felt as if there were enormous mountains crashing down upon over and over again in rapid succession. He felt as if all of the bones in his body had been shattered, making it impossible to defend take any evasive measures.

To compound his woes even further, he could feel his own consciousness beginning to fade in the face of the devastating barrage of attacks.

His True Extreme Film had already been shattered long ago, exposing his body directly to the wrath of E Kuai's fists, and only now did he come to realize that there was still a massive gap between them.

It seems like this is the end...

Right at this moment, a voice rang out in his mind.

"Fellow Daoist Li..."

The voice sounded as if it belonged to Daoist Xie, but it was also a little unfamiliar at the same time, and Han Li wanted to respond, but was unable to even muster up the spiritual sense required to do so.

"Do not resist, I'm going to lend you some of my essential spiritual power."

Immediately thereafter, the eyes of the holy remains on the crystal slab abruptly sprang open, and it made a strange hand seal before pointing a finger at its own heart.

After that, it raised its finger, and a burst of golden light flowed out of its chest before converging to form a golden ball at its fingertip.

With a flick of its finger, the golden ball flew into the lake of blood as a streak of golden light.

E Kuai hurriedly raised a hand to try and stop it, but the golden ball passed straight through his hand as if it had no substantial form before flying directly into Han Li's glabella.

"This is... immortal spiritual power!" Shi Chuankong exclaimed in a stunned manner upon detecting the aura emanating from the golden ball, while Gu Qianxun was looking very perplexed, clearly not familiar with immortal spiritual power at all.

Right at this moment, a burst of radiant golden light erupted from the bottom of the lake of blood, as if a radiant sun were rising up from its depths.

Basked within the golden light, E Kuai suddenly realized that his own fists had become incredibly slow. It was as if countless invisible threads had appeared in the surrounding space, latching onto his body to slow him down.

What was even more alarming to him was that even his thoughts had slowed down to a crawl.

A giant, golden wheel had appeared behind him without any warning, and it was giving off waves of time law powers that brought him almost to a complete standstill.

In a testament to E Kuai's incredible power, even though he was in such close proximity to the Mantra Treasured Axis, he was still not completely immobilized, and he swung around to try and shatter the axis, but Han Li naturally wasn't going to give him that opportunity.

A burst of golden lightning sprang forth as an Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword burst out of Han Li's body. It seemed to be ecstatic that it had finally been called upon after so long, and it flew directly at E Kuai.

There was very little distance between Han Li and E Kuai at the moment, so the tip of the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword pierced into the latter's lower abdomen in the blink of an eye, but E Kuai's body as so incredibly resilient that even the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword was only able to just barely pierce into the outer wall of his dantian.

Right at this moment, a thunderous roar rang out from down below, and Han Li drew upon all of his remaining immortal spiritual power and physical prowess to slam a hand into the end of his sword's hilt with all his might.

A dull thump rang out as the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword was slammed into E Kuai's dantian, following which it released an arc of golden lightning.

E Kuai let loose a drawn-out cry of agony as a hole was blasted into his dantian, out of which a plume of black smoke rose up into the air.

Immediately thereafter, the black coloration of his skin began to slowly fade, and he stumbled back a few steps before falling onto his back.

Chapter 983: Awakening

Han Li struggled to his feet, then limped over to E Kuai before pulling out the Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword lodged in his dantian, following which he decapitated E Kuai with a swing of the sword.

Right at this moment, his Mantra Treasured Axis and Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Sword returned to his body on their own, lacking the immortal spiritual power required to support them.

His entire body was riddled with wounds, but a smile appeared on his face as he took a glance at Violet Spirit, following which his legs gave out from under him, and he sat heavily down onto the ground.

Meanwhile, Mistress Liu Hua, Gu Qianxun, and Shi Chuankong were all looking on with astonished expressions.

"E Kuai is dead... just like that?" Gu Qianxun murmured to herself, while Mistress Liu Hua and Shi Chuankong remained in a stunned silence.

Han Li forced himself to sit up, then took a deep breath before closing his eyes.

The golden ball in his body was rapidly shrinking, and the flow of immortal spiritual power in his body was quickly stagnating again.

While the immortal spiritual power was still able to circulate, he hurriedly retrieved some recovery pills from his Flower Branch domain.

He had used up almost all of the recovery pills in his possession, and the pills in the Scalptia Spatial Domain couldn't even begin to compare with the pills from the outside.

After retrieving a sufficient supply of pills, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he reached into the front of his own robe before pulling out a black statue amid a flash of black light.

It was the statue that he had obtained from Daoist Master Bone Shine.

After doing all of this, the golden ball in Han Li's body completely faded away, and his immortal spiritual power circulation became stagnant again.

Han Li took one of the recovery pills, and his injuries quickly began to heal.

"Are you alright, Fellow Daoist Li? I must say, you never fail to astonish and impress," Shi Chuankong said as he strode over to Han Li.

"I'm fine," Han Li replied, then made his way over to Violet Spirit to carefully inspect her condition, upon which he was relieved to discover that her injuries weren't particularly severe.

He then strode over to E Kuai before sweeping his spiritual sense over his body, only to discover that he wasn't carrying anything.

How could this be?

Storage treasures couldn't be used in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so everyone was carrying many things on their bodies, such as pills and weapons, yet none of those things appeared to be in E Kuai's possession.

Right at this moment, Han Li's gaze fell upon a bone ring that E Kuai was wearing on his left hand.

The ring was giving off a faint white glow, indicating that it was no ordinary ring.

As Han Li removed the ring from E Kuai's finger, Mistress Liu Hua suddenly said, "You've got a keen eye. That ring is a storage treasure that I crafted by incorporating starpower and spatial restrictions, and it can be used with starpower."

Han Li took a glance at Mistress Liu Hua upon hearing this, then injected his starpower and spiritual sense into his ring.

A layer of white light surfaced over the bone ring to keep out his spiritual sense, but he was easily able to break through the layer of white light with his starpower, allowing his spiritual sense to enter the ring.

The space within the ring wasn't very large, only around twenty to thirty feet in size, far smaller than even the most rudimentary storage treasures in the outside world, but this was an extremely precious treasure in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

The internal space of the ring was laden with all types of items, including pills, weapons, beast cores, and scriptures.

Han Li quickly examined these items with his spiritual sense, and his eyes lit up as he discovered a pair of statues sitting in a corner of the storage space.

These were none other than the two remaining statutes of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, and Han Li was ecstatic to see them, but he refrained from pulling them out of the ring in order to avoid attracting attention.

He withdrew his spiritual sense before placing the bone ring onto his own finger, then transferred his two statues and the pills that he had just retrieved into the ring.

Right at this moment, a burst of crimson light shot out of the nearby lake of blood, and it quickly wrapped itself around E Kuai's body before dragging it into the depths.

Han Li cast his gaze toward the holy remains with a contemplative look on his face, and right at this moment, Sha Xin slowly regained consciousness.

Her body was in shambles, but she was still able to just barely struggle to her feet.

Almost at the exact same moment, Violet Spirit also opened her eyes, and an ecstatic look appeared on Han Li's face upon seeing this.

"Where's E Kuai?" Sha Xin asked in an alarmed voice as she frantically took in her surroundings.

"Rest assured, City Lord Sha, E Kuai has already been slain by Fellow Daoist Li," Mistress Liu Hua said with a smile.

A mix of relief and bewilderment appeared in Sha Xin's eyes as she turned to Han Li, and right as she opened her mouth to say something, Daoist Xie's authoritative voice rang out from the center of the lake.

"Alright, E Kuai is already dead, so none of you need to be here anymore. I'm going to ask all of you to leave with the exception of Fellow Daoist Li."

The blood in the lake was currently still converging toward the holy remains, and at this point, it had already completely regrown a body of flesh and blood.

The body was that of a silver-haired middle-aged man with a square face, and even though his eyes were tightly shut, he was still giving off an aura of regal authority.

The middle-aged man was rather similar in appearance to Daoist Xie, but not completely identical.

"Master! You're alive!" Sha Xin exclaimed as her voice trembled with elation and excitement, and she paid no heed to her own injuries as she fell to her knees and kowtowed to the ground.

"I'm still not completely recovered yet, so I'm going to need to spend some time to rest and recuperate, and Fellow Daoist Li on his own will suffice to protect me," Daoist Xie continued.

"Fellow Daoist Li may have played a vital role in killing E Kuai, but he's still an outsider, so I think it would be best for me to stay and protect you, Master," Sha Xin said in a hesitant manner.

"Fellow Daoist Li and I have been together for many years, so there's no need for you to worry about his character. On top of that, I have another important mission for you..."

Daoist Xie's voice trailed off here, and he continued to communicate to Sha Xin through voice transmission.

After hearing what Daoist Xie had to say, Sha Xin gave a firm nod, then turned to Han Li as she said, "I'll be leaving Master to you then, Fellow Daoist Li."

Immediately thereafter, she turned to depart with Violet Spirit.

"Please wait a moment, City Lord Sha," Han Li hurriedly called out after her. "Violet Spirit is my friend, so please undo the restrictions in her soul so that she can be restored to her normal mental state?"

A series of mixed emotions surfaced in Violet Spirit's eyes upon hearing this.

"Please forgive me, Fellow Daoist Li, I completely forgot all about this," Sha Xin exclaimed as she slapped a hand to her own forehead. "Back when Violet Spirit first arrived in Puppet City, I was worried that she could be a spy sent by Profound City, and that's why I sealed away her memories. I'll undo the seal right away."

With that, she quickly made a string of hand seals, then extended a finger, resting it on Violet Spirit's glabella.

Rays of golden light flowed out of her fingertip and into Violet Spirit's glabella, and a series of golden lines appeared on her forehead to form a rune.

At the same time, a dazed look appeared on her eyes, and she began to slump down in a feeble manner.

As she did so, the golden rune on her forehead disintegrated into countless specks of golden light, and she gave a muffled groan as she fell unconscious.

Han Li immediately sped over to her side, catching her before she could fall, following which he turned to Sha Xin and asked, "What happened to her?"

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, she's only temporarily lost consciousness, and she'll regain consciousness soon," Sha Xin replied with a faint smile, then extended a parting curtsey toward the middle-aged man at the center of the lake of blood before departing, accompanied by Mistress Liu Hua and Gua Qianxun.

Shi Chuankong turned his gaze to Han Li, and he opened his mouth to say something, but held his tongue in the end before also making his way outside.

Before long, Sha Xin and the others had arrived outside the underground cave.

Sha Xin closed the entrance to the passageway, then sat down with her legs crossed, and a faint layer of white light emerged over her body, while Mistress Liu Hua and the others stood nearby.

After a long hesitation, Mistress Liu Hua gritted his teeth and strode over to Sha Xin with Gu Qianxun by his side, then extended a respectful bow as he declared, "City Lord Sha, I've come with my daughter, Gu Qianxun, to pay our respects."

"There's no need for such formalities, Fellow Daoist Liu Hua. Is there something you would like to speak to me about?" Sha Xin asked as she opened her eyes.

"Now that E Kuai is dead, it's only a matter of time before you establish your rule over the entire Scalptia Spatial Domain. I was a fool to have allied myself with E Kuai, and I'm hoping that you can forgive me for my misguided ways out of the kindness of your heart. I am willing to pledge my subordination to Puppet City from now on, and I implore you to accept me," Mistress Liu Hua said in an earnest manner.

"I am also willing to join Puppet City. Please accept us, City Lord Sha," Gu Qianxun said as she also extended a deep bow.

"You want to join our Puppet City? Setting aside your daughter for now, you've helped E Kuai create countless star artifacts in the past, causing immeasurable damage to our Puppet City. Even if I'm willing to accept you, how can you expect everyone else in our Puppet City to be so gracious?" Sha Xin asked in a cold voice.

"To make amends for my past transgressions, I'm willing to give you a detailed rundown of all of the distributions of forces around Profound City, as well as the weak points in the city's protective array. Will that suffice as atonement?" Mistress Liu Hua asked with a wry smile.

Sha Xin's eyes immediately lit up upon hearing this, and she said, "It would be remiss of me to turn you down after you've displayed such sincerity. From this day forth, both of you are now citizens of our Puppet City."

"Thank you, City Lord Sha," Mistress Liu Hua said in an elated manner as he extended another deep bow with Gu Qianxun.

Chapter 984: Long-Awaited Reunion

After hearing the conversation between Mistress Liu Hua and Sha Xin, Shi Chuankong approached the latter, then cupped his fist in a salute as he asked, "Can I speak to you about something, City Lord Sha?"

"Go ahead, Fellow Daoist Shi," Sha Xin prompted.

"Can we speak in private?" Shi Chuankong asked.

A sharp gleam flashed through Sha Xin's eyes as she scrutinized Shi Chuankong, while the latter looked back at her with a composed smile.

The sharp gleam in Sha Xin's eyes faded as she nodded in response, and the two of them distanced themselves slightly from Mistress Liu Hua and Gu Qianxun before engaging in a conversation through voice transmission.

......

In the underground space.

Han Li carried Violet Spirit over to a patch of flat ground before setting her down.

After that, he fed her a recovery pill before sitting down to watch over her.

Close to an hour flew by in a flash.

Right at this moment, Violet Spirit's brows furrowed slightly, and a faint moan escaped her lips as she opened her eyes.

"How are you feeling?" Han Li asked with an excited look in his eyes.

As Violet Spirit turned to him, her eyes were no longer looking dazed at all, and it was clear that she had recovered all of her mental faculties.

Her entire body stiffened as she stared blankly at Han Li, and she reached out to gently stroke his face as she asked in a disbelieving voice, "Is it really you?"

"It's me. I'm sorry I wasn't by your side all these years," Han Li replied in a gentle tone as he latched onto her delicate hand.

The two of them stared at each other in silence, and it seemed that both of them were basking in the joy of reunion.

Looking at Violet Spirit's breathtaking features, memories of their past flashed through Han Li's mind one after another, from their first encounter in the Scattered Star Sea, to the time they spent in the Heavenvoid Hall, the Umbra Realm, and Devilfall Valley. After that came their journey through the Great Jin, leading up to their separation following Han Li's ascension...

All of these memories were still fresh in Han Li's mind, as if they had only taken place yesterday, but as he looked back over them, it was as if they were memories from a past life.

Violet Spirit seemed to have also begun reminiscing about the past as she gazed upon Han Li, and after a long silence, she said, "I didn't know how long it was going to take for me to find you after I ascended. I certainly wasn't expecting to see you so soon and under circumstances like these."

"I just so happened to arrive in the Devil Realm under a series of coincidental circumstances. Otherwise, who knows how long it would've taken for us to reunite?" Han Li replied with a smile.

"By the way, I recall that I was taken to Puppet City by City Lord Sha after arriving in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so why am I here now? And what is this place?" Violet Spirit asked.

"We're in the Great Ruins deep within the Scalptia Spatial Domain right now. After you went ot Puppet City, Sha Xin placed a seal on your soul, and that's why you can't remember anything up to this point..."

With that, Han Li gave Violet Spirit a rundown of everything that had happened since their initial meeting in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and after hearing what Han Li had to say, Violet Spirit smiled as she said, "I see. It's a good thing that City Lord Sha didn't harbor any bad intentions toward me. Otherwise, perhaps our reunion would've never happened."

"Neither of us know Sha Xin very well, so it's still important to be careful around her," Han Li warned.

"I know, I'll make sure to be on my guard," Violet Spirit replied in an obedient manner.

"By the way, what happened after I ascended? How were you able to ascend so soon? Given your aptitude, I would've expected you to take longer to ascend," Han Li said in a perplexed manner.

"You just want to ask about Big Sister Nangong, right? If so, then just ask. Why ask in such a roundabout fashion?" Violet Spirit scoffed with a roll of her eyes, and a sheepish look appeared on Han Li's face upon having his intentions seen through.

"Rest assured, I paid a visit to the Spirit Realm prior to transcending my ascension tribulation. Everything was going well in the Azure Origin Palace, and Big Sister Nangong's cultivation was also progressing quite smoothly. At the time, she was already at the Grand Ascension Stage and preparing for her own ascension tribulation.

“As for how I was able to ascend so soon, it's a long story, but long story short, I stumbled upon some fortunate circumstances that allowed me to ascend ahead of Big Sister Nangong and the others," Violet Spirit said.

Han Li's expression remained unchanged upon hearing this, but internally, he was feeling quite relieved.

"You were using an orthodox human cultivation art, so you should've ascended to the Immortal Realm, right? How did you end up in the Devil Realm?" Violet Spirit asked.

"I did indeed ascend to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region in the True Immortal Realm, and it was a long sequence of events that led me to the Devil Realm," Han Li replied.

"I haven't been in the Devil Realm for very long, but even I'm aware that the Devil Realm and the Immortal Realm are sworn enemies of one another, so why is it that you seem to be on very good terms with a prince of the Night Sun Empire?" Violet Spirit asked.

"That's a long story..."

In response to Violet Spirit's question, Han Li gave her a brief rundown of the events that transpired since his ascension, keeping only the matters regarding the Heaven Controlling Vial secret from her.

Violet Spirit's expression changed over and over again as she listened to Han Li's story, and she couldn't help but be stunned by his tumultuous experiences.

In particular, she was very touched to hear how Han Li was willing to venture into the Scalptia Spatial Domain to search for her, and even long after Han Li was finished with his story, she was still staring off blankly into space, processing what she had just heard.

"I knew you were always destined for great things, but it's still nothing short of astonishing for me to hear that you've already reached the High Zenith Stage. You must've endured countless hardships to reach your current heights," Violet Spirit sighed.

"I did encounter some perils along the way, but it's all in the past now. Besides, if it wasn't for these perils and hardships, I wouldn't have been able to progress so quickly, so I suppose they were ultimately all blessings for me," Han Li replied with a nonchalant smile.

"That's a good way of looking at things," Violet Spirit said with a smile of her own. "What are your plans from here onward?"

"I promised Fellow Daoist Xie to keep a lookout for him while he recuperates. Once he's made a full recovery, I'll leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain, then find a way to return to the True Immortal Realm," Han Li replied.

"He has a way to allow us to leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain?" Violet Spirit asked with a surprised expression.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit. Once I've made a full recovery, I'll be able to draw upon the essential power of the Scalptia Spatial Domain to teleport you two lovebirds out of here," Daoist Xie interjected in an amused voice, and a deep blush instantly appeared on Violet Spirit's face upon hearing this.

"Come with me to the True Immortal Realm, Violet Spirit. As long as you have enough Devilish Origin Stones, you'll be able to cultivate in the True Immortal Realm just the same," Han Li proposed in an earnest manner, and Violet Spirit fell silent upon hearing this.

Han Li was very familiar with her personality, and he made no effort to rush her.

After a brief silence, Violet Spirit suddenly said, "Brother Han, there's a question that I've been wanting to ask you for a very long time."

"Go ahead," Han Li prompted.

"Which one is more important to you, me or Big Sister Nangong?" Violet Spirit asked as she looked straight into his eyes.

Han Li was rendered speechless upon hearing this, and only after a long silence did he reply with a forced smile, "Why would you ask that? Both you and Wan'er are extremely important to me."

Violet Spirit continued to look at Han Li in silence, while Han Li felt more and more sheepish by the second.

A hint of disappointment flashed through her eyes upon hearing his answer, but it quickly faded away, and she sighed, "It's always the more the better for you men, isn't it?"

Han Li heaved an internal sigh and offered no response.

"I don't have a habit of relying on anyone, and I don't plan to change that anytime soon, so I'm going to continue cultivating on my own for now. From what you've told me, you have some very formidable enemies, so you would only be weighed down by me. Hence, it's better for me to remain in the Devil Realm," Violet Spirit decided after a long silence.

"You haven't changed at all," Han Li sighed with a wry smile. "What are your future plans?"

"My cultivation aptitude is far inferior to yours, but it seems like I have some talent in the art of puppet manipulation, so I plan to continue following City Lord Sha as her disciple. Once Fellow Daoist Xie makes a full recovery, I'll probably leave this place to cultivate in the Devil Realm," Violet Spirit replied.

"In that case, I won't try to dissuade you, but do accept these things. They'll be very helpful for your future cultivation," Han Li said as he pulled out a few jade slips, making copies of the cultivation art on the first statue of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, as well as two devilish cultivation arts that were suitable for Violet Spirit.

Chapter 985: Separation Following Reunion

Violet Spirit didn't refuse Han Li's offerings, but her expression instantly changed slightly after she inspected the contents of the jade slips with her spiritual sense.

Her cultivation base wasn't particularly advanced, but she had accumulated some knowledge and experience during her time in the Black River Water Palace and Puppet City, so she could tell that these were all extremely precious cultivation arts.

"I can tell that you've already made good progress in the Puppet Heart Technique, but when it comes to honing spiritual sense, no cultivation art can match the Spirit Refinement Technique. If you can master the Spirit Refinement Technique, your puppet manipulation abilities will be sure to benefit immensely.

“However, there are very severe risks involved in pursuing this cultivation art, and I've laid out those risks in detail in the jade slip, and it's up to you whether you would like to cultivate it or not. Make sure to cultivate the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts diligently as well. Once you've opened a profound acupoint, the corresponding immortal acupoint will be far easier to open," Han Li said.

"I understand," Violet Spirit replied with a nod, then stowed the jade slips away.

"As for the other two cultivation arts, I obtained both of them from a Great Encompassment Stage devilish cultivator. You won't be able to cultivate them for now, but they fit quite well with your physical constitution, so you can save them for the future.

“However, you can begin cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and the Spirit Refinement Technique right away. You can stay here to cultivate while I keep a lookout for Brother Xie. That way, I'll be able to give you some instruction in your cultivation," Han Li continued.

"There's no need for that. I plan to return to City Lord Sha's side. My puppet manipulation techniques still have much room for improvement, and I'll make sure to put these cultivation arts to good use as well. I'll be sure to look after myself, so there's no need to worry about me," Violet Spirit replied as she averted her gaze.

"In that case, take this with you as well. I obtained this puppet from one of the Puppet City cultivators, and it's quite powerful, so keep it for your own protection. Even if Sha Xin finds out about it, she won't say anything if you tell her that it's from me," Han Li said he offered her the golden ball that was the Gold-Winged Falcon puppet.

"That's a Gold-Winged Falcon!" Violet Spirit exclaimed at the sight of golden ball, and she hesitated momentarily, but still accepted it in the end.

"You've given me so many things, but all I can give you in return is this," she said as she handed a translucent green jade pendant to Han Li.

However, the jade pendant wasn't complete, and it seemed to be only half a pendant. Furthermore, its edge was rather jagged and uneven, seemingly indicating that someone had forcibly snapped the jade pendant into two.

There was a glowing image in the center of the jade pendant, depicting a humanoid figure.

Han Li's expression changed slightly as he looked up at Violet Spirit, and the latter said in a determined voice, "There's no need for you to do anything about this, I'll take care of it myself. I just wanted to tell you about it."

After that, she turned to depart.

Han Li took a step forward and reflexively reached out to stop her, but ultimately refrained from doing so as he heaved a faint sigh.

Before long, Violet Spirit emerged from the underground space, where she was greeted by the sight of a small gathering of people, consisting of Sha Xin, Mistress Liu Hua's trio, Zhuo Fa, Hei Da, and Hei Er.

"City Lord Sha," Violet Spirit greeted as she extended a respectful curtsey.

"Why did you come out, Violet Spirit? How is my master?" Sha Xin hurriedly asked with a surprised expression.

"That senior is still recovering at the moment, and I've come out after speaking briefly with Fellow Daoist Li," Violet Spirit replied.

Sha Xin nodded in response, then latched onto Violet Spirit's hand as she said in an apologetic manner, "Forgive me for placing that seal on your soul. I did it for the sake of Puppet City, but it must've been very hard on you."

"It's fine, City Lord Sha, I understand why you did it," Violet Spirit assured.

Sha Xin was quite relieved to hear this, and she asked, "What are your plans from here onward?"

"I want to continue serving you, City Lord Sha," Violet Spirit replied in a determined manner.

......

Following Violet Spirit's departure, a vortex suddenly appeared on the surface of the lake of blood in the underground cave, and the crimson crystal slab was sucked into the depths along with Han Li.

Immediately thereafter, Han Li and Daoist Xie appeared in a large crystal palace together.

The walls of the palace were completely transparent and crimson in color, and there were all types of runes engraved upon it, giving it the appearance of a larger version of the crystal coffin from before.

The crystal slab that was carrying Daoist Xie's holy remains slotted perfectly into a stone platform on the ground, and it was as if they had been one to begin with.

There were three ring-shaped troughs on the ground in the crystal palace, and they were also etched with complex runes.

It seemed that the entire hall was a giant star array.

As Han Li swept his gaze over the area, he discovered that E Kuai's body was laying in one of the nearby troughs.

"I've fused as one with this set of remains, but I'm still far from completing a full resurrection. Hence, I'm going to need to rest and recuperate here for some time, and I'll need you to protect me during this time, Fellow Daoist Han," E Kuai suddenly said.

"Why do you want me here as opposed to Sha Xin? Isn't she your subordinate? And she seems to be very loyal to you," Han Li asked with a puzzled expression.

"E Kuai was also one of my closest subordinates, and I even tasked him with protecting this place, but how did that work out? In the end, he colluded with the Devilish Monarch and almost destroyed this entire Scalptia Spatial Domain. Right now, you're the only one I can trust," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"How exactly are you related to the Devilish Monarch? Why did he plot against you?" Han Li asked.

"That's... a long story. I'll tell you about it after I'm fully recovered. There are two side palaces in this Starfall Crystal Palace, one one the left, and one on the right. One of them was where I used to research bodily refinement puppetry, and all of the scriptures I left behind should still be in there. You can browse those materials as you please.

“As for the other side palace, that was where I cultivated in the past, and you can use that place for your own cultivation for now," Daoist Xie said.

Han Li nodded in response, choosing not to ask any further questions.

Moments later, a circular array appeared above the crystal palace, and a burst of bright starlight quickly illuminated the entire array.

At the same time, the walls and ground of the crystal palace also began to glow radiantly, and immense starpower was converging from all directions.

The patterns on the crimson crystal slab and the stone platform beneath it lit up in unison, forming a crimson light barrier that encompassed Daoist Xie's body within it.

At the same time, the sound of flowing water rang out from within the troughs on the ground, and the blood from the lake began to pour in, filling all three ring-shaped troughs before flowing collectively toward the crimson stone platform at the very center of the palace.

Han Li could clearly sense the tremendous bloodline power within the blood slowly fusing into Daoist Xie's body.

Right at this moment, a dull thump rang out, and Han Li turned to discover that E Kuai's body had abruptly exploded without any warning, and his flesh and bones were all pressed tightly against the wall of the trough by some type of invisible force.

As his remains were submerged by the blood from the lake, his flesh and bones began to slowly melt away, disintegrating into pure bloodline power that injected itself into the array.

Right at this moment, Han Li felt his own heart shudder violently, following which a deep, unnatural flush appeared on his face.

He was slightly alarmed by this as he began channeling the starpower within his own body while making his way toward the side palace on the right.

Upon entering the side palace, he immediately sat down with his legs crossed.

At this moment, all of the blood in his body was pumping forcefully through his veins, and it was as if it had been brought to a boil. Plumes of pink mist were also pouring incessantly out of his pores, as if his skin had been set alight.

All of his true spirit bloodlines also began to churn violently, threatening to erupt out of his body, and he was struggling to keep them under control.

He immediately channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and all of the starpower in his body to try and suppress the true spirit bloodlines, but that only lent them more power, making them even more violent, to the point that even his bones had begun creaking and groaning.

What's happening?

All of a sudden, he recalled how his true spirit bloodlines had become far more powerful when used in conjunction with his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

Given that his true spirit bloodlines were currently working against him, it was naturally not a good idea to enhance them.

With that in mind, Han Li hurriedly stopped channeling his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, only using the starpower in his body instead to soothe the raging true spirit bloodlines.

Only after a full four hours had passed did the unrest in his true spirit bloodlines gradually begin to subside, but his cheeks were still looking slightly flushed.

He opened his eyes as he exhaled, then heaved a faint sigh as he murmured to himself, "This could prove to be troublesome..."

After that, he rose to his feet and took a glance at his surroundings.

There were eight white jade bookshelves that were around ten feet in height in the side palace that he was in, and they were all laden with scriptures of different descriptions.

At the very center of the palace was an octagonal crystal pagoda that was also around ten feet tall, and it had nine levels in total, with spiritual light swirling around it, presenting a beautiful sight to behold.

Chapter 986: Calm and Focused

Han Li passed by the nearby bookshelves, and only upon reaching the crystal pagoda did he discover that there weren't any runes engraved upon it, nor was it any type of immortal treasure. Instead, it was just a special storage structure.

Each level of the pagoda was split up into eight grids, placed in each of which were many jade slips and scriptures.

The bottom level was the one with the largest area, and it was also the one that had the most scriptures, most of which were in the form of books and scrolls. The scriptures were densely packed together, and each grid contained around a hundred of them.

Each successive ascending level was smaller than the previous one, so there were fewer scriptures inside, and the top level only contained eight scriptures, all of which were jade slips.

Having been given permission by Daoist Xie to access the scriptures as he pleased, Han Li didn't hesitate to pick out one of the jade slips before pressing it against his own glabella to inspect its contents.

Moments later, he set the jade slip down with an intrigued expression.

The jade slip contained a puppet refinement cultivation art called the Hundred Refinement Puppet arts.

The cultivation art was very complex, and just in terms of material selection alone, there were three sub-categories, laying out the environmental, timing, and human factors that had to be taken into consideration. Furthermore, there were very detailed descriptions of how the use of different materials would affect the puppet that was refined, as well as how different environment and timing factors impacted the puppet refinement outcome.

However, Han Li was currently more interested in looking at some scriptures related to bodily refinement, hoping to find something that could suppress or resolve the issue of his true spirit bloodline backlash.

Hence, he promptly returned the Hundred Puppet Refinement Arts to its original spot before continuing to examine some other jade slips.

......

Seven days flew by in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed in a corner of the hall, carefully reading through a scroll that was titled "Origin Star Blood Refinement Arts".

Compared with other bodily refinement cultivation arts, which generally instructed one in how to refine their physical bodies, this one was very bold and innovative, proposing the possibility of using starpower to directly refine one's blood.

Using this cultivation art, one would be able to accumulate large amounts of starpower in their blood, so if they were to sustain any blood injuries during battle, they would be able to use the blood that flowed out of their wounds against their enemies, often catching the enemy off guard.

On top of that, the more starpower one accumulated in their blood through the use of this cultivation art, the more drastically their powers would be enhanced by the use of certain blood-incinerating secret techniques.

However, the cultivation process was extremely difficult and perilous, requiring one to directly guide starpower into their own bloodstream, which was an excruciating and high-risk procedure.

If one were to lose control of the starpower in their blood as it passed through certain vital regions like their heart or dantian, then that could spell instant death.

Han Li was very intrigued by this cultivation art, but he had no intention of pursuing it as it was explicitly stated that this cultivation art wasn't suitable for those with special bloodlines.

This was because cultivators with special bloodlines would find it more difficult than the average cultivator to integrate starpower into their blood. Given how complex Han Li's bloodline already was, pursuing this cultivation art would be no different from committing suicide.

However, there were certain parts of this cultivation art that were useful to Han Li for reference purposes. In particular, the methods laid out to quell potential unrest in the starpower in one's blood were very insightful for Han Li.

Hence, his intention was to extract the useful parts of the cultivation art and incorporate them into his own cultivation.

Some time later, he closed the scroll, then massaged his own temples as he rose to his feet and placed it back onto the crystal pagoda.

Over the past few days, he had read through all of the scriptures on the pagoda, but he hadn't found much useful information.

Even the Origin Star Blood Refinement Technique couldn't completely resolve the problems that he was currently facing.

However, there were some bandaid solutions laid out in the cultivation art that he was eager to try out.

With that in mind, he left this side palace and made his way toward the other one.

As he passed by the star array at the center of the palace, he noticed that Daoist Xie had already been completely enveloped within a layer of dense crimson light, making it impossible to see him from the outside.

As soon as Han Li entered the other side palace, he felt as if his entire body had been enveloped in a burst of gentle, warm pressure that provided an extremely comfortable sensation.

He inspected his surroundings momentarily to discover that the entire area was riddled with all types of runes, and flashing star designs had been engraved onto the ceiling and the ground beneath his feet.

Bursts of rippling white light were sweeping over these flashing stars, presenting a stunning sight to behold.

The starpower here is extremely abundant. As expected of Brother Xie's former place of cultivation...

Han Li strode over to a lotus flower cushion at the center of the palace before sitting down onto it with his legs crossed.

A burst of white light instantly appeared beneath his backside, and it was as if he had just sat down onto a soft and warm padded chair.

After taking a seat, he took a moment to collect himself, then began running through the Origin Star Blood Refinement Arts in his mind, but didn't begin cultivating it right away.

He ignored the part of the cultivation art that detailed how to incorporate starpower into one's blood, choosing to only examine the parts that laid out how to quell and suppress the starpower in one's blood.

According to the cultivation art, starpower was very similar in nature to true spirit bloodlines in that if it were to spiral out of control, then it would simultaneously incinerate one's blood essence while also bursting through one's blood vessels, resulting in self-detonation.

Given Han Li's tremendous physical constitution, he was fairly confident that he would be able to avoid the fate of self-detonation, but he would still inevitably perish if all of the blood essence in his body were incinerated into nothingness.

Only after some extensive contemplation did Han Li commence his cultivation.

......

Over eight years flew by in a flash.

Inside the side palace, Han Li was seated with his legs crossed atop the lotus flower cushion. At this moment, his skin was as red as blood, and plumes of pink mist were rising up from his body, transforming the surrounding area into a pink sauna.

His eyes had also turned bright red, but he was looking very calm and collected as he made a strange hand seal while chanting an incantation, following which he gently laid down to his right with one hand supporting his own head, looking as if he were about to take a nap.

As soon as he adopted this pose, the starpower in his body instantly surged through his entire body from head to toe, then back to his head, going back and forth in a stable fashion to slowly suppress his violent true spirit bloodlines.

The bright red coloration of his skin also slowly faded away, returning to his normal complexion.

I've finally done it! Looks like all this time and effort hasn't gone to waste!

Han Li rolled over and sat back up as a pleased smile appeared on his face.

Over the past eight years, Han Li had spent some time browsing through the scriptures in the other side palace, but the majority of his time had been spent cultivating the Origin Star Blood Refinement Arts in seclusion.

After countless attempts, he had finally begun to master the way to quell his own true spirit bloodlines.

Han Li rose to his feet and stretched lazily as he looked up at the flashing stars engraved onto the ceiling above. The stars formed a series of constellations that hung up in the sky like jade belts, presenting a beautiful and ethereal sight to behold.

He was in quite a good mood, and he murmured to himself, "Looks like it's another bright and starry night."

He had discovered very early on that even though this crystal palace was situated beneath the lake of blood, it was connected with the sky outside, and whenever night fell, the stars on the ceiling would light up just like the stars in the sky.

The clearer and brighter the night sky was, the brighter the stars in the palace would glow, and the more abundant the starpower that they would release.

After observing the stars on the ceiling for some time, a thought suddenly occurred to Han Li, and he rummaged around in the front of his own robe momentarily before pulling out the Heaven Controlling Vial and setting it down onto the ground.

The light cascading down from the ceiling shone down onto the vial, basking it in a gentle glow, clearly illuminating all of the patterns on its surface.

However, even after waiting for a long while, the vial didn't display any change at all.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly as he murmured to himself, "Looks like the starlight produced by these stars still can't match..."

All of a sudden, his voice abruptly trailed off as a layer of hazy white light appeared around the vial, and the entire vial took on a translucent appearance as a series of specks of white light took shape around it, forming a giant white halo that was giving off a soft glow.

However, the rate of accumulation of specks of white light was quite slow, far slower than what could be achieved through the absorption of organic starlight.

Han Li observed the Heaven Controlling Vial for a moment longer before stowing it away again. He had only brought it out as an act of curiosity, and he wasn't actually planning to manifest any spirit liquid with it. After all, he had no use for the vial's spirit liquid in the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

After stowing the vial away, he stood up and made his way to the other side palace.

......

One day, roughly a month later.

Han Li was seated with his legs crossed, and he pulled four items out of his sleeve before setting them down in front of himself one by one.

The four items were four ancient statues that seemed to depict some type of devilish being with three heads and six arms, but each of them were displaying different expressions and poses.

Chapter 987: Rapid Progress

A contemplative look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he examined the four statues.

The one on the very left was one that he had obtained from Green Goat City, and he had already fully mastered the three levels of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts enclosed within it during his time in the Weeping Blood Array.

The second and third statues had both been in E Kuai's possession, while the final statue was the one that he had pulled out of the Flower Branch domain.

According to E Kuai, there were four of these statues, so he had completed the set.

A hint of concern appeared in Han Li's eyes at the thought of the Flower Branch domain.

At the time, he was on the verge of running out of the immortal spiritual power imparted upon him by Daoist Xie, so he was only able to pull out this statue and some recovery pills, and he wasn't even able to go into the domain.

Weeping Soul was still lying unconscious on the second floor of the bamboo pavilion, and Han Li had no idea if her condition had worsened at all.

However, there was simply nothing that he could do at the moment.

In the wake of Shi Pokong's betrayal, his ticket back to the Devil Realm had been proven to be counterfeit, so the only way for him to return to the Scalptia Spatial Domain now was to wait for Daoist Xie to make a full recovery.

Furthermore, now that Shi Zhanfeng was dead, there was naturally no way for him to fulfill his promise of getting the grand priest to treat Weeping Soul's condition.

On top of that, the battle for the throne in the Devil Realm was only going to become more and more intense, and Han Li didn't want to deepen his involvement in this matter.

After taking a moment to collect his thoughts, Han Li picked up the second statue, then took a deep breath, following which a burst of translucent light shot out of his glabella and into the statue.

Immediately thereafter, the statue began to cycle through a series of strange poses, and with each pose that it adopted, a passage of profound text would appear on its back, laying out the next three levels of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

Han Li stared intently at the statue and began to imitate its movements.

......

On a continent that was countless kilometers away, a seductive woman was seated on a white jade chair in a majestic palace at the center of a massive city, listening to a report being delivered by a handsome young man.

The woman was none other than Sha Xin, while the report was being delivered by Zhuo Fa.

"We've established firm control over Profound City. There's been some minor resistance from the four subsidiary cities, but they've all been quelled. Also, Gu Qianxun has made some significant contributions during this process," Zhuo Fa reported in a respectful manner.

"I heard that the elders and subordinates that formerly served under Qin Yuan of Profound End City all surrendered and pledged their subordination to our Puppet City, but they were still all killed nonetheless. Why is that?" Sha Xin asked.

"Gu Qianxun was responsible for that, but she was acting under Mistress Liu Hua's instructions. He told me that he would explain the matter to you in person," Zhuo Fa replied after a brief hesitation.

"They must've just been settling some personal vendettas. Let them do as they please," Sha Xin said in an indifferent manner.

"In Gu Qianxun's defense, she did make a clear effort to keep the damage to a minimum. All of the battles were held in the arena in Profound End City, and there were a total of eighty-one battles spanning over a period of seven days and seven night before all of Qin Yuan's former subordinates were killed. As a result, there were no innocent civilian casualties or any collateral damage," Zhuo Fa said in a careful manner.

"It sounds like she was quite measured in her approach. Her actions are hardly of consequence. Have new city lords been instated yet?" Sha Xin asked.

"Mistress Liu Hua is currently serving as the temporary city lord of Profound City, and Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing have pledged their subordination to him as well, so that was actually the smoothest transition. As for the other cities, city lords have also been assigned, but a lot of people have died in the process," Zhuo Fa reported.

"Profound City is no smaller a city than our Puppet City, so make sure to keep it under thorough supervision at all times," Sha Xin instructed.

"Yes, City Lord Sha," Zhuo Fa replied.

"How many of the ruins that I instructed you to excavate have you found?" Sha Xin asked.

"At this point, we've only found twenty-one, and we're still searching for the remaining eighty-seven," Zhuo Fa replied.

"These ruins are spread out over the entire Scalptia Spatial Domain, and some of them in very perilous and completely uninhabited places, so you've already made some good progress finding twenty-one of them in such a short time. Just make sure you find all of them within the next one thousand years," Sha Xin said.

Zhuo Fa gave an affirmative response.

"This is a vital matter for Master's resumption of control over the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so it must be treated with the utmost care and diligence," Sha Xin said in a serious manner, then waved a hand to dismissive Zhuo Fa, who extended a respectful bow before promptly departing.

......

Inside an underground secret chamber in a large manor in the western region of Puppet City, Shi Chuankong was submerged within an octagonal pool of blood with his body bound by eight translucent, crimson chains, each of which was attached to one of the eight crimson stone pillars around the pool.

The chains were clanging incessantly, and the eight crimson stone pillars were also trembling violently as the entire pool of blood churned and bubbled while giving off bursts of scorching heat.

However, Shi Chuankong's body remained completely still, as if he were completely unaffected, and only his tightly furrowed brows and the audible grinding of his teeth betrayed the fact that he was in excruciating pain.

However, he had willingly put himself in this position. In fact, he had to make a deal with Sha Xin for this privilege.

Right at this moment, a speck of light appeared on his chest as a profound acupoint was abruptly opened.

......

Over eight hundred years passed by in the blink of an eye.

The star array in the crystal palace beneath the lake of blood was still operating, while bursts of rumbling were ringing out incessantly within one of the side palaces.

Inside the side palace was a strange-looking humanoid creature with golden fur all over its body, a pair of lightning wings on its back, and pieces of azure turtle shell all over its arms.

The humanoid creature was currently pounding the walls of the side palace with all its might, but thankfully, the tremendous starpower released by the runes on the walls ensured that the building wasn't completely razed to the ground.

The monstrous creature pounded the walls for a full six hours before its strength finally began to wane.

As its movements slowed down, the silver wings on its back faded away, quickly followed by the chunks of turtle shell on its arms, then the golden fur all over its skin.

After all of these features faded away, the humanoid figure was revealed to be none other than Han Li.

His eyes were sunken deep into his face, and he looked completely emaciated. He was having to support himself with his palms against the ground, and he was panting heavily while sweating profusely, but his sweat was being evaporated into steam as soon as it oozed out of his pores, making it appear as if his entire body were enshrouded in a cloud of mist.

Some time later, he slumped down against the wall, and the rampant true spirit bloodlines in his body finally settled down again.

Ultimately, true spirit bloodlines were still different from starpower, and the Origin Star Blood Refinement Technique alone was struggling more and more to quell the unrest in his true spirit bloodlines.

At this rate, this will only have to happen a few more times, and all of my blood essence is going to be incinerated into nothingness...

Han Li heaved a faint sigh at this sobering thought.

He had already read through all of the scriptures in the other side palace no fewer than ten times, and none of the scriptures related to bodily refinement had presented any solutions. Surprisingly enough, he was able to find a potential solution in a scripture related to puppetry, but it was one that he was very reluctant to pursue.

The method involved refining a powerful puppet and transferring one's true spirit bloodlines into it, then drawing in someone else's blood into one's own body in order to ensure survival.

However, if he were to do this, then his powers would be significantly diminished, and the resulting puppet would temporarily possess extremely formidable combat prowess, but once it used up all of the blood essence in its body, then it would be reduced to a useless piece of trash.

Even though Han Li was very resistant to the idea, he knew that he would have to resort to it for his own survival if no better solution was found.

During this time, Daoist Xie had awakened several times, and Han Li had taken advantage of those opportunities to open the Flower Branch domain to check on Weeping Soul.

All of the Purple Sun Warm Jade had already been used up, but for some reason, her condition hadn't continued to worsen. Hence, Han Li temporarily sealed Weeping Soul away using a puppetry secret technique taught him by Daoist Xie so that he could address her condition another time.

On top of that, Han Li also asked Daoist Xie if the latter had any solutions pertaining to his problem of true spirit bloodline backlash.

After all, Daoist Xie was the one who had instructed him to cultivate the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to begin with, and this backlash had only begun to arise after he used the advanced refinement method enclosed in the cultivation art to refine his own true spirit bloodlines.

Daoist Xie's explanation for this was that his true spirit bloodlines had to have been enhanced following the refinement process, thereby resulting in this backlash.

Unfortunately, he wasn't able to provide any solutions, and he told Han Li that he would address the matter once he came out of seclusion.

Hence, Han Li had no choice but to continue cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts to enhance his own physical constitution while suppressing his true spirit bloodlines with the starpower in his own body. As long as he didn't use his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts in conjunction with his true spirit bloodlines, the latter wouldn't be enhanced any further.

Hence, he became even more diligent in his cultivation of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

At this point, he had already mastered the first six levels of the cultivation, completing the second statue, and he had opened over nine hundred profound acupoints, making him comparable in power to E Kuai prior to his death.

The main factors that contributed to his astonishingly rapid progress in the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts were the tremendous amount of bloodline power stored in the Heaven Controlling Vial, as well as the special environment in this crystal palace.

Chapter 988: Fusion

Even with such ideal factors at his disposal, Han Li was still struggling to make progress in the third statue.

This was because the cultivation method laid out in the third statue had changed, and it was no exaggeration to say that it was completely different from before.

It required the cultivator to use starpower to open profound acupoints while simultaneously using their bloodline power to facilitate a physical transformation, essentially turning one into a devilish being with three heads and six arms.

Tremendous bloodline power was required to accomplish this. Otherwise, it would be impossible to manifest all three heads and six arms at once.

Han Li's bloodline power was already quite immense, but it was still not quite up to scratch.

Han Li was sitting on the ground with a contemplative look in his eyes when a faint smile suddenly appeared on his face, and he pulled the jade pendant given to him by Violet Spirit out of the front of his robe before carefully examining it.

The pendant was slowly revolving over the palm of his hand, depicting a faintly glowing figure inside. The more Han Li examined the jade pendant, the more perplexed he became.

Why did she give this to me? It doesn't appear to be special in any way. The only thing noteworthy about it is that the figure inside looks a little like me. Is this what she's been using to remember me by?

He lifted the jade pendant up by its string, then gave it a twirl with his fingers, and the pendant immediately began to revolve rapidly in mid-air, doing so with such incredible speed that the afterimages it left behind resembled a green ball.

At the same time, a three-dimensional image of the figure inside the pendant appeared within the green ball.

Han Li's expression suddenly changed slightly upon seeing this, and an intrigued look appeared in his eyes as he murmured to himself, "Perhaps that's feasible..."

Immediately thereafter, he pulled out the four statues again before setting them down in front of himself for a close examination.

The third statue laid out a method of using one's bloodline power to alter their physical body. Han Li couldn't accomplish this with his bloodline power alone, but what if he were to use his true spirit bloodlines instead?

Han Li had taken inspiration from the jade pendant. The pendant and the figure inside it didn't necessarily have to be separate entities. Instead, perhaps they were better viewed as a single combined entity.

However, this raised a new concern.

The previous few instances of true spirit bloodline backlash had all stemmed from his usage of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts. If he were to channel both at once, was there a chance that could trigger even more violent true spirit bloodline backlash.

After some extensive contemplation, he ultimately decided to give it a try. At this point, his true spirit bloodline backlash had become such a dire problem that he had to take some drastic measures to address it right away.

With his mind made up, Han Li didn't hesitate any longer, and a burst of translucent light shot out of his glabella and into the third statue.

Han Li had already memorized all of the statue's poses, so on this occasion, most of his attention was focused on the contents of the passages of profound text that appeared on its back, particularly the method required for one to alter their physical form with their bloodline power.

Only after thoroughly reading through all of the relevant material did he begin imitating the movements of the statue, and as he did so, all of his profound acupoints lit up one after another.

At the same time, he also began channeling his true spirit bloodlines, and it didn't take long before a burst of heat flashed through his body.

Han Li was very familiar with this sensation. It was the precursor to true spirit bloodline backlash, and it wasn't going to take long before his blood began boiling in his veins.

He did his best to compose himself, and instead of using his starpower to soothe the unrest in his true spirit bloodlines, he began guiding his true spirit bloodlines toward his shoulders and back in accordance with the routes laid out in the third statue.

However, as soon as he did this, his true spirit bloodlines immediately began to surge toward his head like floodwaters through a broken dam.

Han Instantly felt a tearing pain in his shoulders, and the muscles there began to bulge as new flesh began to grow.

At the same time, a burst of sharp, unbearable pain speared through Han Li's consciousness, making it feel as if his spiritual sense were in the process of being torn apart.

Even with Han Li's incredible pain tolerance, the combination of physical and spiritual agony was still almost too much for him to bear, and he couldn't help but let loose a guttural roar.

However, what was rather surprising to him was he was feeling very lucid and conscious, and that was why he was able to feel the agony so clearly and intensely, but at the same time, this also did seem to prove that this was a feasible approach.

With that in mind, Han Li gritted his teeth tightly and began to focus wholeheartedly on cultivating the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts.

......

Over five hundred more years flew by in a flash.

Inside one of the side palaces of the crystal palace, layers of crimson light were flashing incessantly, and within the crimson light was a man that was around a hundred feet tall, with three heads and six arms.

The man was currently seated with his legs crossed on a lotus flower platform, repeatedly cycling through a series of strange movements with his six arms.

Of his three heads, the middle one was that of a golden ape, the one on the left resembled that of a true dragon, while the one on the right belonged to a giant eagle-like bird.

All of a sudden, the man joined all three sets of his palms in front of himself, and the crimson light around him slowly faded away.

Simultaneously, his body gradually shrank down, and by the time all of the light had faded away, Han Li was revealed, fully in the nude.

He exhaled as he opened his eyes, then twisted his neck from side to side as a faint smile appeared on his face.

Ever since he discovered that his true spirit bloodlines could be used to cultivate the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, he had been cultivating diligently without rest, and even though he hadn't opened any additional profound acupoints, his body had undergone a massive transformation.

What was most pleasing to him was that the true spirit bloodline backlash problem had already been half-resolved, and the reward for his efforts was that devilish form that he had just displayed.

By using the cultivation art laid out in the third statue, he was able to draw upon his Giant Mountain Ape, True Dragon, and Kun Peng bloodlines at once. Hence, when he adopted that devilish form with three heads and six arms, he possessed the power of all three types of true spirits, thereby granting him incredible power.

At this point, the threat of backlash from these three true spirit bloodlines had already been resolved, and the same method could be used to resolve the threat posed by his other true spirit bloodlines as well.

Han Li's guess was that after he mastered all twelve levels of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts, he would attain four different forms with three heads and six arms, just like the four statues, and each form would have a set of three different true spirit heads.

However, there was an element of randomness to this process, and he wasn't entirely sure what the final outcome was going to be.

After taking a brief rest, Han Li was just about to stand up to take a walk when the entire crystal palace suddenly began to tremble violently, and all of the patterns on the walls and the ground began to light up on their own.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he hurriedly rushed out of the side palace.

Upon reaching the entrance of the main palace, Han Li was greeted by the sight of Daoist Xie, enshrouded in a layer of radiant white light.

Dense clusters of profound acupoints were flashing all over his body, and after a quick count, Han Li determined the number of profound acupoints to be one thousand eight hundred!

After hovering in mid-air for a while, a tremendous aura abruptly erupted out of Daoist Xie's body, and even with Han Li's powers, he was kept out by this incredibly formidable aura, unable to take even a single step into the palace.

Could it be that Brother Xie has already reached the Dao Ancestor level?

All of a sudden, Han Li noticed another figure laying beside Daoist Xie. This figure's entire body was golden in color, and their eyes were tightly shut, seemingly in a state of slumber.

Han Li was quickly able to determine that the golden figure was a puppet, but at the same time, there was something strange about its aura, as if there were something sealed inside it.

Daoist Xie slowly opened his eyes, and two beams of dazzling golden light shot out from within.

The golden light rapidly spread to encompass Daoist Xie's entire body, then quickly filled the entire palace, and even Han Li was encompassed within it.

Han Li was ecstatic to discover that while basked in the golden light, his immortal spiritual power was able to resume normal circulation, and he immediately took advantage of this opportunity to open the Flower Branch domain so that he could inspect Weeping Soul's condition with his spiritual sense.

In doing so, he discovered that Weeping Soul's condition hadn't changed, and that was quite a relief for him.

Enshrouded within the golden light, Daoist Xie's body took on a rather indistinct appearance, and all of a sudden, he looked up at the sky before abruptly vanishing from the spot.

In the next instant, he appeared in the sky above the Myriad Opportunity Palace, and the golden light radiating from his body became even brighter, making him resemble a resplendent golden sun.

Hei Da and Hei Er were stationed outside the palace, and both of them were stunned to see this.

As the golden light shone down upon them, the surrounding spatial pressure faded away, and the devilish qi in their bodies began to circulate again.

However, the two of them had been in the Scalptia Spatial Domain for too long, so most of their devilish qi had already dissipated, and as a result, this change was barely detectable to them.

Chapter 989: Heavenly Dao Tribulation

With Daoist Xie's departure, the radiant golden light in the crystal palace also faded away.

Han Li felt the circulation of immortal spiritual power in his dantian slowing down again, but it didn't completely stagnate as the previously ever-present spatial pressure had disappeared.

After taking a moment to compose himself, he used his spiritual sense to track down Daoist Xie, then drew upon his own sluggish immortal spiritual power to unleash a movement technique to arrive outside the palace in the blink of an eye.

As he became basked in the golden light again, the circulation of his immortal spiritual power returned to normal.

At this moment, Daoist Xie was standing with his hands by his sides, looking up at the heavens with excitement and anticipation in his eyes.

Han Li followed his gaze and also looked up at the sky, upon which he discovered that the previously clear skies had become very dark, and the yellow clouds above were also rapidly turning black.

At the same time, a burst of tremendous pressure was quickly building in the air, and Han Li was forced to plummet back down onto the ground, as if a massive mountain had fallen upon him.

This is the aura of a major tribulation!

The aura of this imminent tribulation was countless times more powerful than any tribulation that Han Li had faced in the past, the pressure was only continuing to mount further and further.

Hei Da and Hei Er were standing on the ground, so they were subjected to far less pressure than Han Li, but even so, their legs were still trembling incessantly, while their complexions had turned very pale.

"Get away from here! This is not something that you can withstand," Daoist Xie commanded in an authoritative voice, and Hei Da and Hei Er immediately fled into the distance.

Meanwhile, Han Li had already vanished from the spot amid a flash of golden lightning even before receiving this verbal warning from Daoist Xie, and he reappeared several hundred kilometers away turning his gaze back to Daoist Xie.

At this point, he was already too far away for the golden light radiating from Daoist Xie's body to reach him, and he only took a quick glance back at Daoist Xie before continuing to flee into the distance, covering another several hundred kilometers in the blink of an eye.

Even after getting this far away, the sky up above was still inky black, and more dark clouds were continuing to rapidly converge from all directions, clearly indicating that he still hadn't flown out of the area encompassed under the tribulation yet.

The sky was looking even darker than before, and even the ground below had been plunged into complete darkness.

Han Li was stunned to see this, and he hurriedly continued flying away into the distance.

Right at this moment, all of the dark clouds in the sky suddenly began to revolve rapidly in a certain direction while simultaneously converging toward the center, forming an enormous vortex that stretched as far as the eyes could see.

Bolts of black lightning were flashing incessantly throughout the vortex, illuminating the ground below like fireworks.

A black hole quickly appeared at the center of the vortex, and it was releasing a faint glow, seemingly leading to an unknown place.

A burst of pressure that was countless times more formidable than before erupted out of the vortex, causing the nearby space to tremble and warp violently, and the pressure came crashing down directly upon Han Li.

Even though he had already opened over nine hundred profound acupoints, he was still completely powerless to resist the unfathomable pressure, and he quickly lost consciousness.

However, prior to falling unconscious, he caught sight of a vast gray cloud flying out of the center of the massive vortex before making its way toward Daoist Xie.

The cloud was very normal in appearance, but it was giving off a devastating aura, and it was precisely this aura that had knocked Han Li unconscious.

......

Inside a black palace in Night Sun City.

The Devilish Monarch was enshrouded in a layer of soft silver light, forming a large ball of silver light that was slowly revolving around him, and the space around the ball of light was rippling visibly as it revolved.

All of a sudden, his eyes sprang open, and the silver light around him instantly faded as he cast his gaze out of the palace, and a cold look flashed through his eyes as he slowly rose to his feet.

......

Inside the Balance Fall Duke's manor, Shi Pokong was standing in a courtyard, looking into the distant sky with a contemplative look on his face.

......

Han Li had fallen into a terrifying nightmare. He felt as if his body had been submerged at the bottom of a boundless glacial sea, and tiny bursts of glacial power were seeping into his body, putting him in excruciating pain.

After what seemed like an eternity, the surrounding glacial power gradually faded away, following which a burst of warmth injected itself into his body, filling him with a blissful sensation.

Han Li slowly awakened, and he discovered that he was laying on the ground.

The sky above had turned purple, and there was a warm and gentle aura in the air.

All of a sudden, he recalled what had happened prior to him falling unconscious, and he hurriedly turned his gaze toward the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

Daoist Xie was still standing in mid-air, and his entire body was charred black and riddled with massive wounds, giving him the appearance of a tree that had been struck by lightning.

A vibrant, purple cloud was gradually taking shape at the center of the vortex above him, and it slowly descended to encompass him before rapidly seeping into his body.

As a result, his injuries began to heal at a rate that was discernible even to the naked eye, and he was fully healed in the blink of an eye.

All of the purple light in the sky quickly converged to form a single band of purple radiance, and a burst of translucent light abruptly shot out of Daoist Xie's body to fuse as one with the purple light.

A burst of rumbling rang out as the band of purple light instantly swelled to several times its original size, then began circling around Daoist Xie like a roaming dragon.

Countless translucent threads could be seen within the purple light, giving off tremendous law power fluctuations.

Han Li was enveloped by these law power fluctuations, and his body began to move involuntarily like a puppet on strings.

The nearby ground was also beginning to tremble violently, but thankfully, the band of purple light only revolved around Daoist Xie for a short while before vanishing into his body, and the tremendous law power fluctuations that it was giving off faded along with it.

At this moment, Daoist Xie's entire body was shrouded in purple light, and his eyes were tightly shut, seemingly inspecting his own internal condition.

Moments later, all of the purple light faded away to reveal Daoist Xie.

A purple robe had appeared over his body, and he didn't appear to be any different from before, but every single movement of his now seemed to be imbued with power that could move the very world around him.

However, in the next instant, the unfathomable power emanating from his body faded away, as did the purple clouds in the sky.

All of a sudden, everything had returned to normal.

Han Li slowly rose to his feet, still feeling a little lightheaded.

Hei Da and Hei Er were currently lying on the ground close to a hundred kilometers away, and they seemed to be in worse condition than Han Li. Both of them were still unconscious at the moment, but thankfully, they had fled in a timely manner, so they most likely weren't in any life-threatening danger.

Daoist Xie turned his gaze to Han Li, and with just a single step, he appeared directly beside Han Li as if by instantaneous teleportation.

"I didn't anticipate that my Heavenly Dao Tribulation would arrive so soon and encompass such a large area. If I had known this would happen, I would've told all of you to get away earlier," Daoist Xie said, then swept a sleeve through the air, and the lightheaded sensation that Han Li was feeling was instantly erased.

Hei Da and Hei Er also shuddered slightly, and even though they were still unconscious, they were gradually beginning to recover from their injuries.

"That was a Heavenly Dao Tribulation? Could it be that you've already become a Dao Ancestor?" Han Li exclaimed with a stunned expression.

"Indeed. After countless years of arduous cultivation, I've finally managed to ascend to the peak," Daoist Xie confirmed with a smile.

"Congratulations."

Even though Han Li had already guessed that this was the case, he still couldn't help but be a little stunned to hear this, and he cupped his fist in a congratulatory salute.

"Please allow me to thank you, Fellow Daoist Han. It was only with your help that I was able to get to this point," Daoist Xie replied as he returned Han Li's salute.

"You're far too kind, Senior, and Han Li is fine. I wouldn't dare to be referred to as a fellow daoist by a Dao Ancestor," Han Li hurriedly said.

"We've been together for many years, and I trust you more than anyone, so there's no need to observe such dogmatic formalities, Fellow Daoist Han. My surname is Shi, but you can continue calling me Daoist Xie," Daoist Xie said with a dismissive wave.

"In that case, I'll oblige. By the way, did you just say that your surname is Shi?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. My name is Shi Kongjie. I didn't intentionally hide this from you, I simply failed to recall my name this entire time, and many things happened after we entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so I didn't get a chance to tell you," Daoist Xie confirmed with a nod.

"Shi Kongjie... Could it be that you have some ties with the Night Sun Empire?" Han Li asked.

Daoist Xie looked up into the sky and offered no response.

"If you don't want to answer the question, then just pretend like I never asked," Han Li said.

Now that Daoist Xie was a Dao Ancestor, Han Li couldn't help but feel a little cautious and apprehensive around him.

"No, it's fine, Fellow Daoist Han, I was simply reminiscing about the past. It's only thanks to you that I was able to reach this place, so you deserve to know the truth. On top of that, I have another request for you, and in order to fulfill this request of mine, you'll need to know these things anyway," Shi Kongjie replied with a faint smile.

"What do you need me to do?" Han Li asked.

Chapter 990: It All Goes Back to the Golden Crab

"This is not a good place to talk. Let's go back underground first," Daoist Xie said, then swept a sleeve through the air, and Han Li instantly felt his own body enveloped within a burst of gentle force, immediately following which he found himself in the underground palace.

The other golden Daoist Xie in the crystal palace had already awakened, and there were two other humanoid puppets standing beside it.

The other two puppets were also identical to Daoist Xie in appearance, but one was pitch black, while the other was a pristine white.

The black puppet was glowering at Daoist Xie with intense murderous intent in tis eyes, while the white puppet had a warm and pleasant smile on its face, looking much more benevolent and approachable.

Han Li turned to Daoist Xie with a perplexed expression, while the three puppets were also all looking at him.

The golden puppet didn't say anything, and it only took a brief glance at Daoist Xie before looking away.

Meanwhile, a cold look appeared on the black puppet's face as it sneered, "You may have been fortunate enough to transcend your Heavenly Dao Tribulation, but I'm still going to kill you and take your place eventually!"

As for the white puppet, it maintained its warm and friendly smile as it said, "Congratulations, Fellow Daoist. May I ask why you've summoned us to meet you here?"

"I have some tasks for the three of you. Fellow Daoist Black Spirit, please travel to Puppet City to inform Sha Xin that I've come out of seclusion," Daoist Xie instructed as he turned to the black puppet.

The black puppet seemed very reluctant to do his bidding, but it still obliged and departed, nonetheless.

"Fellow Daoist White Spirit, please undo the spatial restrictions around the Great Ruins and guide all of the citizens of Puppet City here," Daoist Xie continued as he turned to the white puppet, which also promptly departed.

"Fellow Daoist Golden Spirit, I need you to go and make some preparations. I'm going to draw upon the essential power of the Scalptia Spatial Domain to open a spatial passageway that'll allow Fellow Daoist Han here to return to the Holy Realm," Daoist Xie said to the golden puppet, and it nodded response before departing as well.

An intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face as he watched the three puppets depart one after the other.

"You seem to be very curious about those three puppets, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie remarked as he sat down onto a chair, then invited Han Li to take a seat as well.

"I am. These three puppets all seem to possess sentience. What types of puppets are they?" Han Li asked.

"Given your knowledge and experience, I'm sure you already have a guess, right?" Daoist Xie asked with a faint smile.

"You've seen right through me, Fellow Daoist Xie," Han Li chuckled. "Could it be that these three puppets are related to the three corpses that you've severed?"

"You're correct, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie confirmed with a nod. "I severed my three corpse souls and sealed them into these three puppets."

"I've heard that the three corpse souls are always a major problem for Great Encompassment cultivators. They can't be killed as doing so would pose some risk to the cultivator, but keeping the three corpse souls around is also very dangerous as they could turn on you at any moment.

“That's why the cultivators of the Heavenly Court have gone out of their way to seal their corpse souls into the Gray Realm. In light of that, it's brilliant that you were able to seal your three corpses into these puppets and make them do your bidding," Han Li praised with an impressed expression.

"Indeed, the three corpse souls are very difficult to manage, and the majority of Great Encompassment cultivators and Dao Ancestors will choose to seal them away. I'm only able to keep them by my side without any qualms thanks to my mastery in the laws of puppetry," Daoist Xie explained.

Han Li nodded in response, then said, "Let's get back on track, Fellow Daoist Xie. What do you need me to do for you?"

"There's no hurry, Fellow Daoist Han. Listen to my story first. Just as you guessed, I have some ties with the Night Sun Empire. I am the younger brother of the current Devilish Monarch, Shi Kongyu, which makes me Shi Chuankong's uncle," Daoist Xie declared, and Han Li was quite astonished to hear this.

"In that case, why are you in the Scalptia Spatial Domain? And judging from the conversation that I overheard between E Kuai and City Lord Sha, it sounds like you're currently enemies with the Devilish Monarch," Han Li said.

"That's a long story that goes all the way back to when we were competing against each other for the throne. Long story short, I was defeated, and he stripped me of the spatial laws that I had arduously cultivated. Thankfully, I was able to escape with the help of some others, and I fled into the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Daoist Xie explained.

Han Li didn't display any outward reaction to this, but internally, he was stunned to hear this.

He had many questions that he wanted to ask, but this matter clearly concerned certain secrets of the Night Sun Empire, so he didn't raise any questions.

"I'm assuming Shi Kongyu wouldn't have let you off the hook so easily, right?" he asked.

"Of course. Shi Kongyu appears to be quite noble and generous, but in reality, he's a very petty and spiteful man. However, the Scalptia Spatial Domain has been a special space within the Holy Realm ever since ancient times, and anyone who sets foot in here will have their cultivation bases completely suppressed.

“On top of that, cultivators at or above the Great Encompassment Stage can't even enter this place at all, and that's how I was able to survive in here," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"Why is it that Great Encompassment cultivators aren't able to enter this place? Is Shi Kongyu not a Dao Lord himself? How is this restriction able to take effect on him?" Han Li asked with an incredulous expression.

"The Scalptia Spatial Domain was created by an ancient Dao Ancestor, and it's precisely because of the excessively forceful nature of this restriction that the balance of the Great Dao in this place was damaged, thereby resulting in this place being reduced to the barren wasteland that you see today," Daoist Xie explained.

"I see," Han Li mused as he looked around with an awestruck expression.

At his current cultivation base, he was only able to use his own law powers to affect a certain area around him, and once he withdrew his law powers, everything would return to normal.

However, this ancient Dao Ancestor's law powers were able to have a permanent effect on the entirety of the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and that was a level of law power mastery that Han Li couldn't even begin to fathom.

"You haven't reached this level yet, so all of this must sound very far-fetched for you, but given your aptitude, I'm sure you'll reach this level soon," Daoist Xie said with a smile.

"That's very kind of you, Fellow Daoist Xie. By the way, if such laws exist in this place, then how were you able to come in here and ascend to become a Dao Ancestor?" Han Li asked.

"After my law powers were stripped away by Shi Kongyu, my cultivation base plummeted all the way down to the High Zenith Stage, and that's why I was able to flee into this place. Furthermore, I was fortunate enough to have received that ancient Dao Ancestor's inheritance, making me half an owner of the Scalptia Spatial Domain, so the rules here do not apply to me," Daoist Xie explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a nod. "So how did you end up becoming a puppet and traveling to the Spirit Realm?"

"In this place, I wasn't able to make any further progress in my laws of space, so I switched to cultivating the laws of puppetry instead, which was the law power mastered by that ancient Dao Ancestor. I had exceptional aptitude in the laws of puppetry, and with the assistance of the inheritance left behind by that Dao Ancestor senior, I was able to reach the Great Encompassment Stage and sever two of my corpse souls.

“However, as I was severing my final corpse soul, I was betrayed by E Kuai, who allowed Shi Kongyu to intervene. As a result, my physical body met its demise, so I could only seal my soul and memories into that golden crab puppet and cast it into a lower realm in the hope of resurrecting myself someday, and you know everything that happened after that," Daoist Xie explained.

"So what is it that you need my help with, Fellow Daoist Xie?" Han Li asked.

"Even though I've become a Dao Ancestor, my chances of coming out on top in a battle against Shi Kongyu are still quite slim. Hence, I require allies if I want to avenge myself," Daoist Xie said.

"Could it be that you want me to join forces with you against Shi Kongyu?" Han Li asked with a surprised expression.

"Precisely," Daoist Xie replied with a smile.

"You think far too highly of me, Fellow Daoist Xie. I'm only a mere High Zenith cultivator, how could I possibly provide you with any meaningful assistance?" Han Li asked with a bewildered expression.

"You're too modest, Fellow Daoist Han. While it's true that you won't be able to pose any threat to Shi Kongyu in the near future, I'm certain that you'll reach our level someday, given your tremendous aptitude.

“Now that you've opened so many profound acupoints, you'll be sure to make rapid progress in your cultivation base once you leave this place, so I'm confident that I won't have to wait too long before you become a worthy ally of mine," Daoist Xie replied with a smile.

A hesitant look appeared on Han Li's face upon hearing this.

Even though he and Daoist Xie were close friends, he had already fulfilled his promise to the latter, and if he were to recklessly become involved in a conflict between a pair of Dao Ancestors, then that could easily lead to his demise.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Han, I'm not asking you to stay here right now. Instead, all I ask is that you come back to help me once you've attained sufficient power. On top of that, I'm not asking you to get involved in this matter for no compensation. You can have this as a gesture of my sincerity," Daoist Xie said as he offered a jade vial to Han Li.

Chapter 991: Powerless

Han Li accepted the jade vial, then removed the stopper to discover a ball of white light slowly circling around within the jade vial while pulsing rhythmically as if it were a living creature.

At the center of the ball of light was a white pill that was riddled with countless specks of light, and it was giving off bursts of tremendous life energy.

The aura emanating from the pill was rather similar to that of Daoist Xie's heart, and Daoist Xie explained, "This is a True Profound Pill, which I refined using my own essential energy in conjunction with many other types of precious ingredients. The pill contains a great deal of True Profound Essence, a sufficient amount to support your future progression to the Great Encompassment Stage."

Han Li was both stunned and ecstatic to hear this. He had seen the term "True Profound Essence" brought up many times in scriptures, and it was vital for a breakthrough to the Great Encompassment Stage.

In order to progress to the Great Encompassment Stage, not only did one have to open three hundred and sixty immortal acupoints, most importantly, one had to undergo a process to evolve their soul into a Great Encompassment True Soul, and True Profound Essence was required for this evolutionary process.

True Profound Essence was extremely precious, and it was said that only after passing through heavenly astral winds to reach the extrarealm space would one be able to find small amounts of this essence in the purest and loftiest place in all of heaven and earth.

It was only now that Han Li finally realized that Shi Zhanfeng had most likely entered the Scalptia Spatial Domain in order to obtain sufficient True Profound Essence to facilitate his future Great Encompassment Stage breakthrough.

"You have my thanks, Fellow Daoist Xie," Han Li said as he accepted the jade vial, and Daoist Xie was quite pleased to see this.

"Rest assured, I won't accept something so precious from you free of charge. Once I attain sufficient power, I'll be sure to return and assist you," Han Li promised with a serious expression.

"I'll have to thank you in advance then, Fellow Daoist Han. This True Profound Pill alone is nowhere near enough to make up for everything that you've already done for me, so feel free to call upon me if you need my help with anything in the future," Daoist Xie replied with a smile.

A thought occurred to Han Li upon hearing this, and he said, "Now that you mention it, I really do have something that I require your assistance with."

"Oh? What is it?" Daoist Xie asked.

"I was hoping that you would be able to treat Weeping Soul's condition now that you've become a Dao Ancestor," Han Li replied.

"That's not a problem," Daoist Xie replied with a nod, following which he flicked a finger through the air, releasing a burst of golden light that vanished into Han Li's body before forming a ball of golden light in his dantian.

The surrounding spatial pressure instantly faded, and Han Li's immortal spiritual power circulation was restored once again, allowing him to open the Flower Branch domain.

The two of them immediately made their way to the bamboo pavilion, where Weeping Soul was laying on the bed on the second floor with her entire body riddled with black patterns that formed a seal.

The seal had been placed upon her by Han Li in accordance with a sealing secret technique taught to him by Daoist Xie over a thousand years ago.

Daoist Xie strode over to Weeping Soul's side, and after closely examining her condition for some time, a grim look suddenly appeared on his face.

Han Li's heart immediately sank slightly upon seeing this.

Daoist Xie pressed a finger against Weeping Soul's glabella, and a burst of black light emerged from his fingertip before spreading outward in a series of black ripples.

Weeping Soul instantly shuddered slightly, and it looked as if she were about to awaken.

Han Li was ecstatic to see this, but in the next instant, her body became completely motionless once again.

Daoist Xie's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, and he pressed the palm of his hand flat against Weeping Soul's forehead before releasing another burst of black light, and her body shuddered slightly once again before falling still.

Daoist Xie withdrew his hand with tightly furrowed brows.

"How is she, Fellow Daoist Xie?" Han Li asked in an uneasy manner.

"Her condition is very unique. She seems to have been affected by some type of extremely formidable law powers, causing her soul to constantly dissipate. All I can do is stabilize her condition, but I'm afraid I can't cure her," Daoist Xie replied with a shake of his head.

"If even a Dao Ancestor like yourself can't cure her, doesn't that mean she's a lost cause?" Han Li asked as a hint of despair began to set in.

If even Daoist Xie was powerless to treat Weeping Soul's condition, then even if he could recruit the grand priest's assistance, it most likely wasn't going to amount to anything.

"There's no need to be so disheartened, Fellow Daoist Han. You have to understand that even Dao Ancestors aren't omnipotent. My laws of puppetry do not fare well when it comes to healing. There are countless types of laws in this world, and they're far more profound than you can imagine. Even though I can't save Weeping Soul, I know someone who can," Daoist Xie said with a faint smile.

"Who is it?" Han Li hurriedly asked.

"The grand priest that Shi Chuankong told you about. His law powers specifically target the soul, and he's already reached a very advanced stage of mastery over this law power, so he should be able to cure Weeping Soul," Daoist Xie replied.

"I see," Han Li mused as a spark of renewed hope was ignited in his eyes.

Now that Shi Zhanfeng was dead, it was going to be a lot more difficult to recruit the services of the grand priest. In fact, he would perhaps even have to pit himself directly against the Night Sun Empire, but he had no choice but to do this for Weeping Soul's sake.

With that in mind, Han Li asked, "When can I return to the Devil Realm, Fellow Daoist Xie?"

"Even though I'm now a Dao Ancestor, some preparations still need to be made before I can open a spatial passageway connected to the outside world. On top of that, you're not the only one that I'm opening this spatial passageway for, so let's wait until Sha Xin and the others arrive, which will take roughly half a year," Daoist Xie replied.

Han Li raised no objections to this, and the two of them departed from the Flower Branch domain.

From there, the two of them promptly parted ways, with Daoist Xie departing to make preparations for the opening of the spatial passageway, while Han Li returned to the seclusion side palace.

Before long, Daoist Xie arrived in a hidden secret chamber.

There was only a single oil lamp lit in the secret chamber, basking a small area in dim, yellow light, while the rest of the room remained shrouded in complete darkness.

At this moment, there was a hazy black figure standing beside the oil lamp with their hands clasped behind their back.

Daoist Xie wasn't surprised to see this black figure, and the latter turned around to reveal a set of blurry facial features.

Their body was also rather indistinct in appearance, as if they were nothing more than a projection.

"Congratulations, Fellow Daoist Shi."

"Thank you, Senior. I was too hasty in the past and thought that I could sever all three corpse souls in succession, thereby resulting in an imperfection in my mental state. Even if it weren't for E Kuai's betrayal, I would've surely failed back then. It's all thanks to your guidance that I was able to seal my soul and memories in that puppet to experience the dao of puppetry in a lower realm.

“Now that I've completed the journey from puppet to human, I've finally completely grasped the true meaning behind the laws of puppetry, thereby allowing me to succeed where I previously failed," Daoist Xie said as he extended a grateful bow.

"There's no need to thank me. It's your own aptitude and hard work that have carried you to this point," the hazy figure replied.

"In any case, I'll never forget what you've done for me, Senior," Daoist Xie said in a respectful manner.

"I'm not interested in hearing such empty words of gratitude from you. I've come here this time because I want to ask you if our agreement from all those years ago is still in effect," the hazy figure said.

"Of course. I have no plans of letting Shi Kongyu off the hook after what he did to me," Daoist Xie replied in a cold voice.

A pleased look appeared in the hazy figure's eyes upon hearing this, and he said, "Shi Kongyu has already been ruling over the Devil Realm for a very long time, and he's far too powerful for you to contend with right now. Don't be in a hurry to make any moves, let's take things slowly, one step at a time."

"I understand. Rest assured, Senior, I won't make the same mistake twice," Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"Good. Also, there's something that I require your assistance with," the hazy figure said.

"What is it, Senior?" Daoist Xie asked.

The hazy figure strode over to Daoist Xie before communicating something to him through voice transmission, and Daoist Xie reflexively cast his gaze toward a certain direction as his expression changed ever so slightly.

......

The ball of golden light inside Han Li's dantian contained far more abundant immortal spiritual power than before, and it hadn't run out yet.

Han Li was seated in the side palace with his legs crossed, channeling his immortal spiritual power.

It had been over a thousand years since he had been able to channel his immortal spiritual power so freely, and it was certainly a feeling that he missed greatly.

After remaining dormant in his body for so many years, his time law powers had finally been set free, and his Mantra Treasured Axis instantly appeared behind him.

Immediately thereafter, the Clear Time Vial, the Illusory Dawn Hourglass, the Time Severing Flowing Fire, and the Eastern Vicissitudes Divine Tree all appeared one after another before revolving around him.

Han Li's brows furrowed slightly upon seeing this. All of these time-attribute treasures had appeared on their own outside of his control.

Am I about to transmigrate again?

Right at this moment, flurries of time law threads shot out of the time-attribute treasures, forming a golden ring that began revolving incessantly.

The time law powers within Han Li's body instantly surged into the golden ring, causing it to rapidly expand while simultaneously radiating dazzling golden light and vibrating at a high frequency.

All of a sudden, the Heaven Controlling Vial flew out of the front of his robe as a ball of green light, and it began glowing like a radiant, green sun while releasing a burst of tremendous suction force.

The golden ring began flying toward the vial while rapidly shrinking, and in the end, it shrank down to the same size as the opening of the vial before adhering itself to it.

As soon as contact was established between the two, a burst of formidable time law powers instantly erupted out of the Heaven Controlling Vial.

At the same time, the vial swelled rapidly in size, and countless green runes appeared within it, forming a churning green cloud.

Immediately thereafter, a thick beam of green light shot out of the mouth of the vial before vanishing into the space up ahead.

Chapter 992: Past Events

The space up ahead disintegrated as countless rays of translucent light surged out from within, forming a translucent wall with countless scenes flashing rapidly over its surface.

All of a sudden, a giant vortex appeared on the translucent wall, releasing a burst of tremendous suction force that encompassed Han Li's entire body.

At this point, Han Li was already accustomed to this process, and he merely allowed the suction force to lift him up from the ground.

However, right at this moment, the ball of golden light in his dantian was suddenly snuffed out, and his immortal spiritual power circulation instantly stagnated.

The suction force released by the vortex was also significantly diminished as a result, and Han Li's body drew to a halt before falling back down onto the ground.

However, his soul was sucked into the vortex, and he immediately lost consciousness.

By the time he returned to his senses, he found himself beside the vast river of time.

As usual, the river was formed by countless balls of light, and it didn't appear any different from before.

At this moment, Han Li was hovering beside the river in a spiritual form.

I wonder exactly what this place is...

Instead of approaching the river to enter any of the balls of light, Han Li began to fly in the upstream direction, determined to find out what this place was all about.

In his spiritual form, he was like a cloud floating in the sky, so he wasn't able to pick up much speed.

The scenery in this place was very barren and monotonous, and there was no day-night cycle, either, so the passage of time was rather difficult to track.

By Han Li's estimates, he had already been flying for around seven to eight days, but there was still no observable change in the river beside him.

A hint of impatience was beginning to set in, and he persevered for two more days, but the river still wasn't displaying any change at all.

Forget it. There's no way to tell just how massive this area is, and perhaps this place is nothing more than an illusion, so continuing onward from here would most likely won't be a waste of time.

With that in mind, Han Li stopped in his tracks before turning to the river of time, yet right as he was about to approach it, a small, yellow cloud that was several feet in size suddenly appeared above him.

Within the cloud was a pair of pea-sized black eyes that were fixed on him, and Han Li immediately identified the cloud to be the vial spirit.

The eyes within the yellow cloud blinked a few times, as if they were observing him.

"Do you need something from me?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

As soon as his voice trailed off, the yellow cloud abruptly lit up, following which a streak of translucent yellow light shot out from within.

The streak of light was far too fast for Han Li to evade, and it fused into his soul as a burst of warmth in the blink of an eye.

Han Li was naturally very alarmed by this, yet before he could raise any questions, the yellow cloud vanished into thin air.

After staring for a while up at the spot where the vial spirit had been just a moment ago, Han Li carefully examined his soul's internal condition, but didn't discover anything amiss, nor was he feeling any discomfort.

Hence, he could only put this matter out of his mind for now and make his way over to the river to peer into the countless balls of light inside.

Having already experienced so many transmigrations, it had become clear to him that each ball of light represented a different point in time in the past, and that he could return to a certain point in time by entering the corresponding ball of light.

The Heaven Controlling Vial's transmigratory ability was something that was completely unheard of, and if he could completely control it, then the benefits would be immeasurable.

At the very least, with this ability at his disposal, it would be far easier to examine past events.

However, there were far too many balls of light in the river, and there didn't seem to be any rhyme or reason about them, so there was a significant factor of luck involved in which point in time he would transmigrate back to.

If only I can control which point in time I can travel back to. That way, I'll be able to verify the validity behind Daoist Xie's story.

Now that Daoist Xie had become a Dao Ancestor, some barriers had appeared between them, and they weren't as close as before.

Daoist Xie's story was logically sound and didn't have any holes, but Han Li couldn't help but feel as if some things were being hidden from him.

Right at this moment, the river of time began to ripple violently, immediately following which around a dozen balls of light flew out from all parts of the river before drawing to a halt near Han Li.

An intrigued look appeared on Han Li's face as he carefully examined these balls of light, upon which he discovered that all of them seemed to be depicting the same setting, namely a grandiose palace.

This palace looks a little familiar...

All of a sudden, a flash of realization appeared in Han Li's eyes, and it occurred to him that this palace was a building near the Myriad Opportunity Palace, and judging from the scenes displayed in the ball of light, a fierce battle was taking place in that setting at that point in time.

After some contemplation, Han Li's gaze settled on the largest of the balls of light, and he took a few steps toward it.

A burst of tremendous suction force instantly erupted out of the ball of light, and he lost consciousness once again.

......

After an indeterminate period of time, Han Li slowly awakened to discover that he had possessed a young man in a suit of black armor. He was laying in a semi-collapsed palace, and there was a hole in his dantian that was bleeding profusely.

A semi-transparent wheel of golden light was hovering above his head, with over a thousand Time Dao Runes flashing upon it.

A loud commotion was ringing out incessantly from nearby, indicating that there was a fierce battle taking place.

Instead of immediately rising to his feet, Han Li used his spiritual sense to draw upon the residual memories of his host.

A huge volume of memories instantly flooded into his mind, taking him quite some time to completely absorb.

The man's name was Wu Xuan, and he was a fugitive that had been cast into the Scalptia Spatial Domain. From there, he became Shi Kongjie's subordinate, and thanks to his impressive powers, he was made a personal guard of Daoist Xie.

Daoist Xie had begun cultivating in seclusion over a century ago in order to sever his final corpse soul, and ever since the commencement of his seclusion, the Scalptia Spatial Domain had been placed under a state of lockdown.

However, a large horde of enemies had suddenly infiltrated the Scalptia Spatial Domain on this day, and they stormed all the way to the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

A curious look appeared in Han Li's eyes as he examined Wu Xuan's memories.

He had been wanting to see the sequence of events that had led to Daoist Xie's previous failed breakthrough to become a Dao Ancestor, and it seemed that the river of time had duly obliged. Did this mean that he could already control the destination of his own transmigration?

The more Han Li thought about this, the more he felt like this wasn't just a coincidence. He didn't know how it had happened, but he really had attained an element of control over the river of time.

Perhaps this was the vial spirit's doing, or perhaps it was due to some other reason. In any case, this was certainly great news for him.

Han Li quickly rose to his feet before making his way over to the entrance of the palace, and he could see a series of puppets and cultivators locked in a ferocious battle high up in the sky.

One side consisted of cultivators clad in suits of black armor just like Wu Xuan's, while the cultivators of the opposing camp were all clad in suits of dark purple armor.

These suits of dark purple armor were quite familiar to Han Li as they were assigned to the troops of the Night Sun Empire.

The Night Sun Empire's cultivators were very tall and imposing, and their skin was a dark green color. On top of that, there were tusks protruding out of their mouths, giving them a very fearsome appearance.

There weren't many of them, but they were extremely powerful, possessing extraordinary strength and speed.

The Scalptia Spatial Domain cultivators had the numbers advantage, but they were firmly on the back foot.

Those are Nightmare Dragon Guards. It looks like it really was Shi Kongyu that attacked all those years ago.

During a past conversation, Shi Chuankong had mentioned various secret legions of the Night Sun Empire to Han Li, and one of them was the Night Sun Guards, which consisted solely of bodily refinement cultivators and were directly under the Devilish Monarch's command.

Looking at them now, Han Li could see that these Nightmare Dragon Guards were indeed quite formidable, with each of them comparable in power to a bodily refinement cultivator with a hundred and fifty profound acupoints opened.

Han Li watched the ongoing battle for a moment, then cast his gaze into the distance.

He could see four nine-story pagodas from here, each of which was situated on a corner of a white jade plaza.

At the center of the plaza was none other than the Myriad Opportunity Palace, and the battles were becoming more and more intense closer to the palace.

After a brief moment of contemplation, Han Li adjusted his own armor to conceal the hole in his lower abdomen, then channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique before rushing toward the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

Initially, he was able to remain undetected thanks to his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique, but the closer he drew to the Myriad Opportunity Palace, the more people that he encountered, and ultimately, his cover was blown.

A saber-wielding Nightmare Dragon Guard rushed at him at an astonishing speed while swinging their saber viciously at his head.

Wu Xuan had only opened fewer than two hundred profound acupoints, so he was roughly on par with the Nightmare Dragon Guard in terms of power, but Han Li naturally possessed far superior battle experience and judgment than he did.

Han Li swayed from side to side, conjuring up nine identical afterimages of himself to evade the attack, following which the nine afterimages combined as one again behind the Nightmare Dragon Guard before continuing onward.

The Nightmare Dragon Guard was just about to give chase when they were stopped in their tracks by another cultivator from the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Now that Han Li's cover had already been blown, he made no further effort to conceal his own presence, tapping into every last ounce of power in this body to rush onward as quickly as he could.

The battle raging at the Myriad Opportunity Palace was even more intense than the battles elsewhere, and Han Li ducked behind a semi-collapsed wall nearby before casting his gaze toward the entrance of the palace.

The Scalptia Spatial Domain cultivators were led by none other than Sha Xin, and there were five puppets under her command as she fought against E Kuai, who was clad in a suit of azure armor.

At this point in time, E Kuai only had around six hundred to seven hundred profound acupoints, and the two of them hadn't changed much in terms of appearance over the years.

"How dare you collude with Shi Kongyu to plot against our master! I won't let you leave this place alive!" Sha Xin yelled in a furious voice.

"It's time to face reality, Sha Xin. Shi Kongjie's death is already sealed, so I suggest you pledge your subordination to His Majesty. Given your powers, I'm sure His Majesty would welcome you with open arms," E Kuai said with a smile.

"Preposterous!" Sha Xin harrumphed coldly as her five puppets unleashed a ferocious barrage of attacks at her behest.

Chapter 993: A Battle from the Distant Past

A cold sneer appeared on E Kuai's face as he swung his sword through the air, keeping all of the puppets' attacks at bay.

At the same time, the sword qi that he was unleashing prevented Sha Xin and the five puppets from getting away.

Meanwhile, the Nightmare Dragon Guards had arranged themselves into a defensive formation, doing everything in their power to keep the Scalptia Spatial Domain cultivators out of the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

After taking a moment to assess the situation, Han Li sprang out of his hiding spot, launching himself at the entrance of the palace.

He was immediately spotted by three Nightmare Dragon Guards, which lashed out in unison with their blades to intercept him.

Instead of retreating or taking any evasive measures, Han Li sped up even further while sweeping a sleeve through the air, releasing a long, azure whip, which sprang forth like a spirit snake before wrapping itself around the weapons of the three Nightmare Dragon Guards.

He had picked up the whip from a deceased Nightmare Dragon Guard on the way here, and the three weapons were instantly slowed down slightly by the restrictive whip.

Han Li sped up even further as his skin took on an unnatural, red coloration, and he sped past the three Nightmare Dragon Guards in a flash before continuing on toward the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

He had already made up his mind not to waste any time engaging in any battles, and he was tapping into all of the latent potential in this body to enter the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

Right at this moment, a dark purple figure abruptly appeared before him.

It was an extremely tall and imposing figure, far more massive in stature than the average Nightmare Dragon Guard, and there was a golden dragon head design on the front of his breastplate, indicating that he was a commander.

He swung an arm through the air in a circle, and a burst of black light erupted out of his hand to encompass Han Li from all directions.

As a result, Han Li was instantly slowed down significantly, as if he had been rooted to the spot.

"Pesky little rats should know their place!" the commander sneered as he threw an almighty punch at Han Li, and a gust of fierce black wind erupted out of his fist, but as the wind swept over Han Li's body, he abruptly vanished, as if he had been blown away.

The commander was momentarily rooted to the spot upon seeing this.

Right at this moment, E Kuai called out in an urgent voice, "He's above you!"

The commander hurriedly looked up upon hearing this, and sure enough, Han Li was darting through the air several dozen feet above him.

The red coloration of his skin had become even deeper, but at the same time, his speed had been even further enhanced, and it was already too late for the commander to intercept him.

Since when was Wu Xuan this powerful?

Sha Xin had also noticed what was happening, and a hint of surprise flashed through her eyes.

"Useless!" E Kuai roared in a furious voice as he swung an arm through the air, and close to a hundred profound acupoints lit up over his arm at once.

In the next instant, his sword flew out of his grasp as a black shadow, and it instantly appeared just a few feet behind Han Li before piercing at him from behind.

Han Li's expression changed slightly as he sprang away to the side, but the sword was too fast for him to fully evade, and his left arm was about to be struck.

However, he took no further measures to defend himself as he continued onward, paying no further heed to the oncoming sword.

Right at this moment, a golden shadow flew over from the side before instantly appearing behind Han Li, and it was revealed to be a golden eagle puppet that made a grab for E Kuai's with its talons.

The sword tore through the eagle puppets talons with ease before plunging straight through its chest, but that was the extent of the sword's power, and it was stopped in its tracks.

Han Li was rather surprised to see this, but he continued onward without pause, and there were no further obstacles up ahead, allowing him to rush into the Myriad Opportunity Palace.

E Kuai turned to Sha Xin with a furious expression, while Sha Xin looked back at him with a triumphant smile.

"Send some people after him! We can't allow him to interfere with His Majesty!" E Kuai yelled in an urgent voice.

It seemed that E Kuai was a very authoritative figure among the Night Sun Empire cultivators, and four Nightmare Dragon Guards immediately set off in pursuit of Han Li, while the commander that had let Han Li through also rushed toward the entrance of the palace with a furious expression.

Right at this moment, Sha Xin made a rapid string of hand seals, and two beams of golden light erupted out of the golden eagle puppet's eyes before vanishing into the stone wall beside the palace gates.

Immediately thereafter, the palace gates swung shut with a loud thump.

The four Nightmare Dragon Guards and the commander crashed into the gates of the palace, but it remained completely unmoved.

E Kuai turned to Sha Xin with a look of murderous rage in his eyes upon seeing this.

"The palace gates have already been closed, and there's a restriction placed upon them by Master himself, so there's no way any of you will be able to force your way through!" Sha Xin sneered.

......

Han Li was slightly taken aback to see the palace gates close behind him, but he then quickly turned his attention to the interior of the palace.

As was the case many years later, the interior of the Myriad Opportunity Palace was strewn with shattered furniture and puppet fragments, clearly indicating that a fierce battle had just taken place here.

At this moment, there was no one else in the palace, but the entire area was filled with a sweet-smelling crimson mist.

The mist appeared to be harmless. In fact, it had quite a soothing effect on Han Li instead, who was suffering physically from tapping excessively into the latent potential of Wu Xuan's body.

Once again, he was rather taken aback to see this, but he wasted no time examining this crimson mist as he rushed to the back of the palace.

Sure enough, the black stone chair was still there, and his eyes immediately lit up as he grabbed onto the chair before giving it a twist.

A black passageway that led underground instantly appeared on the ground behind the chair, and Han Li channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique before rushing down the stone staircase inside, quickly reaching the opening at the foot of the staircase.

Beyond the opening was the giant underground cave, and a thunderous commotion was ringing out from within it, causing the entire underground cave to tremble violently.

Han Li arrived beside the opening in a stealthy manner, then took a glance inside to discover that it was looking much the same as it did many years later.

There was a giant lake of blood inside, and at this moment, the lake was rippling violently.

However, there was no crystal coffin at the center of the lake, and in its place was a square, crimson stone platform instead.

There were nine tall, crimson jade pillars standing around the stone platform with countless patterns engraved upon them, and they were giving off radiant crimson light, forming a dense crimson light barrier that encompassed the entire stone platform.

At this moment, Daoist Xie was seated with his legs crossed on the stone platform with his entire body enshrouded in radiant golden light, and his eyes were shut, while his brows were tightly furrowed in a pained expression.

At the same time, his body was trembling slightly, and wisps of gray mist were rising up from all parts of his body before drifting upward, forming a cloud that was around ten feet in size.

The cloud was churning incessantly, and it was beginning to take on a humanoid form.

Meanwhile, there were three figures locked in a fierce battle beside the lake, and their battle was the source of the commotion.

Two of the three figures were the two puppets that contained Daoist Xie's corpse souls, and they were locked in battle against a middle-aged man clad in a suit of purple armor.

Han Li was able to identify the purple figure as Shi Kongyu, but he then immediately arrived at the realization that it was actually a puppet, rather than the actual Shi Kongyu.

Considering how cultivators at or above the Great Encompassment Stage were barred from entering the Scalptia Spatial Domain, it made sense that Shi Kongyu could only be present as a puppet.

The three combatants were all moving at astonishing speeds, and Han Li's eyes were barely able to keep up with their movements.

With each clash that took place between them, a thunderous boom would ring out, sending violent tremors running through the entire underground cave.

However, there seemed to be restrictions placed upon the underground cave, allowing it to remain largely unscathed despite the ferocity of the ongoing battle.

The blood in the lake was also churning violently, throwing up dense clouds of crimson mist that filled the entire underground space.

Shi Kongyu's purple puppet was extremely formidable, with arcs of purple lightning flashing all over its body, and it was racing through the air like a purple lightning dragon, easily leaving multitudes of spatial rifts in its wake.

Daoist Xie's two corpse soul puppets were also extremely powerful, and they were unaffected by the restrictions in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, allowing them to freely use their devilish qi and law powers.

Neither side was able to get the better of the other, and it seemed like there wasn't going to be a decisive outcome anytime soon.

After yet another violent clash, both sides retreated, and the white Daoist Xie said, "Let's put an end to this senseless battle, Fellow Daoist Shi Kongyu. This puppet of yours is quite formidable, but it won't be able to defeat us, so you should just give up and go back. Fellow Daoist Shi is no longer cultivating the laws of space anymore, so he no longer poses any threat to you.

“Hence, you should set aside your past differences and establish a truce. Ultimately, we are all cultivators of the Holy Realm, and the Heavenly Court is our common enemy."

Shi Kongyu gave a cold harrumph upon hearing this, paying no heed to the white Daoist Xie's words as he abruptly vanished from the spot.

The white Daoist Xie's expression changed slightly as it hurriedly sped away to the side, and it had only just managed to move several dozen feet when a fist that was flashing with lightning emerged out of thin air before crashing down upon the spot where it had been standing just a moment ago.

A huge hole was blasted into the space in the path of the fist, and right at this moment, the black Daoist Xie abruptly appeared above Shi Kongyu.

It was wielding a black saber, and as the saber was slashed through the air, a series of black saber projections were unleashed, forming a black lotus flower that descended upon Shi Kongyu.

Chapter 994: It's Me?

Shi Kongyu was completely unfazed by the black Daoist Xie's attack, and he threw a punch in retaliation, sending a burst of purple lightning erupting out of his fist.

The fist and the saber clashed, causing the nearby space to tremble violently, and several spatial rifts were torn into the surrounding area, while Shi Kongyu and the black Daoist Xie were both knocked back by the force of the clash.

However, immediately thereafter, the three of them clashed once again, and all the while, Han Li had been observing the unfolding scene from a hiding spot in the distance.

The events unfolding here were identical to what Daoist Xie had described to him not long ago, so it seemed like Daoist Xie hadn't been trying to deceive him.

Han Li took a glance up at the axis projection above to discover that quite a few of the Time Dao Runes on it had already been snuffed out, and he was beginning to contemplate whether he should leave.

After all, there was no longer much point for him to stay here. In his current body, he couldn't do anything for Daoist Xie, and he already knew that Daoist Xie was going to become a Dao Ancestor in the future, so this crisis wasn't necessarily a bad thing for him.

Right at this moment, a resounding clash rang out, and the battle drew to an abrupt halt.

Shi Kongyu shot back in retreat, stopping near the entrance of the underground cave.

Han Li was quite alarmed to see this, and hurriedly channeled his Myriad Acupoint Tranquility Technique with all his might while concealing himself within a dark shadow.

Shi Kongyu didn't unleash any further attacks, and a faint smile had appeared on his face.

The two corpse soul puppets were rather perplexed to see this, and the white Daoist Xie reiterated, "We are evenly matched, so there won't be a decisive outcome no matter how long this battle wears on for. Hence, you should leave."

"Indeed, I was already aware that my chances of defeating you two were slim to none," Shi Kongyu said with a faint smile, and Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this.

Judging from what Shi Kongyu had just said, it was clear that he had some ulterior motive for engaging in this futile battle against the two corpse soul puppets for such a long time.

The two two puppets had arrived at the same realization as well, and they immediately launched themselves at Shi Kongyu.

Shi Kongyu burst into laughter, and he paid no heed to the pair of oncoming puppets as he suddenly slammed a fist into his own chest.

A fist-sized, gray bone shot out of his body, and there was a black rune that resembled a dried octopus inscribed upon it.

As soon as the gray bone left his body, it immediately erupted into gray flames, and countless black runes could be seen within the flames, forming a human face with a set of features that were twisted in grief, fury, and resentment.

A burst of cold law power fluctuations erupted out of the gray flames in all directions, and all of the restrictive forces in the Scalptia Spatial Domain immediately began to diminish in the face of these law power fluctuations, but didn't disappear right away.

At this moment, Han Li was situated closer to Shi Kongyu than anyone else, so he was the first to be affected by this burst of law powers, and he was instantly struck by a disoriented sensation, as if a burst of invisible, disruptive power had infiltrated his soul.

His soul immediately began to dim, as if a layer of dust had appeared over it, and at the same time, an uncontrollable sense of frustration began to well up in his heart.

At the same time, all types of strange illusions began appearing before him, and this was a precursor of inner demon backlash.

Simultaneously, Han Li was struck by a sense of intense nausea that made him want to puke out all of his internal organs.

What kind of law power is this?!

Han Li hurriedly channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique with all his might to stabilize his own soul while severing his connection with this body that he had possessed.

Pained looks immediately appeared on the faces of the two corpse soul puppets as this wave of foreign law power fluctuations swept over them, and their expressions changed drastically as one of them exclaimed, "You're using the laws of hexes!"

Immediately thereafter, both of them rushed frantically toward Daoist Xie in unison, and two bursts of formidable law power fluctuations erupted out of their bodies to encompass Daoist Xie and the crimson light barrier around him.

Even though they had reacted extremely quickly, they were still just a little too late, and the hex law power fluctuations were able to infiltrate Daoist Xie's body before their law powers could reach him.

At this moment, Daoist Xie was focused wholeheartedly on severing his third corpse soul, and he immediately threw up a mouthful of blood as soon as the hex law power fluctuations entered his body.

The humanoid cloud above his head began to ripple violently, looking as if it were on the verge of dissipating, and Shi Kongyu burst into laughter as he confirmed, "I am indeed using hex law powers. It took me a while to activate this Baleful Hex Bone due to the absence of devilish qi in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but now that I've done it, victory is mine!

“You can never best me, Shi Kongjie. Regardless of what law powers you decide to cultivate, you're destined to be crushed beneath my feet!"

Immediately thereafter, he opened his mouth to release a burst of blood essence onto the gray bone, and the flames around it instantly swelled drastically, while the twisted face within it also became a lot clearer.

Han Li's expression changed drastically upon seeing this, and he forcibly suppressed the extreme discomfort that he was feeling as he fled upward with all his might.

However, he wasn't able to get very far at all before he was struck by an even more formidable burst of hex law power fluctuations, and he felt as if his soul were about to explode as he plummeted to the ground before rolling into the underground cave.

His entire body was trembling uncontrollably, and his hands were clasped over his own head in indescribable agony.

Shi Kongyu immediately swung around with a surprised expression upon hearing the commotion from Han Li's fall, and right at this moment, a black figure appeared before him out of thin air.

It was a black-robed figure with a layer of black mist over their face, and they grabbed onto the gray bone before forcefully tightening their grip, crushing the bone into powder.

The gray flames around the bone exploded, sending a burst of formidable gray shockwaves and fearsome law power fluctuations erupting in all directions.

The black-robed figure clearly failed to anticipate this, and the black mist over their face was scattered slightly, revealing a section of their features. However, the layer of black mist then recovered to conceal their entire face again.

Han Li just so happened to catch a fleeting glimpse of that section of the black-robed figure's face that was revealed, and he shuddered as an incredulous expression appeared on his face, looking as if he had just seen a ghost.

In the next instant, the gray shockwaves swept over his body, sending a burst of even more formidable hex law power fluctuations sweeping into his soul, and his consciousness was instantly fragmented into countless pieces, while his vision faded into darkness.

After what seemed like an eternity, Han Li slowly awakened, having already returned to his own body.

His soul was still aching slightly, but the pain was already countless times less excruciating than before.

As he recalled what he had just witnessed, he abruptly shuddered as he sprang up into a seated position with an astonished look on his face.

It took him a long while to compose himself, but even then, there was still a look of lingering shock in his eyes.

Even though only a section of the black-robed figure's face had been revealed, and only for a brief instant, Han Li was certain beyond a shadow of a doubt that it had been none other than himself!

That face wasn't just similar to his own, it was undeniably his own face!

How is that possible? Could it be that someone disguised themselves as me? But the last time Daoist Xie was severing his corpse souls had to have been countless years before I was even born, so how could anyone have been aware of what I look like? Could it be a coincidence? Maybe there was someone who looked just like me all those years ago?

Han Li's instincts told him that this was no mere coincidence, and he remained seated in a state of stunned contemplation.

Some time later, a burst of door-knocking rang out, snapping him out of his reverie, and he rose to his feet before opening the door to find the white Daoist Xie puppet outside.

"Fellow Daoist Han, Sha Xin and the others have already arrived, and Fellow Daoist Xie has already completed the preparations required to open the spatial passageway, so please come to the main palace," the white Daoist Xie said with its usual benevolent smile.

"It's already been half a year?" Han Li exclaimed.

Could it be that he had been unconscious for half a year after his soul returned to his body?

"That's right," the white Daoist Xie confirmed.

"Alright, I'll come over right away," Han Li replied with a nod, still feeling rather disoriented.

The white Daoist Xie turned to depart, but Han Li suddenly called out to it and asked, "Your name is White Spirit, right?"

"That is the name given to me by Fellow Daoist Shi," the white Daoist Xie replied.

"Fellow Daoist White Spirit, I heard from Fellow Daoist Xie that he was attacked by Shi Kongyu many years ago during his first attempt to sever his three corpse souls, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"Indeed. Shi Kongyu's intervention led to a catastrophic failure for Fellow Daoist Shi on that occasion, but thankfully, he was finally able to overcome this hurdle after all these years of arduous cultivation," the white Daoist Xie replied with a nod.

"You must've been present during that time, right, Fellow Daoist White Spirit? How was Fellow Daoist Xie able to overcome that crisis? Did he receive some form of external assistance?" Han Li asked in a seemingly casual manner while closely observing the white Daoist Xie's expression.

Chapter 995: Farewell, Take Care

"There wasn't much to that crisis back then. Shi Kongyu's powers were almost completely suppressed in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, and his main objective was just to foil Fellow Daoist Shi's breakthrough, so he immediately left after that goal was accomplished.

“As for external assistance, this place is completely isolated from the Holy Realm, and anyone who tried to help us would be pitting themselves against Shi Kongyu, so no one was willing or able to provide us with any external assistance," the white Daoist Xie explained.

"I see," Han Li replied with a contemplative nod.

"I still have some matters to attend to, so I'll be taking my leave now, Fellow Daoist Han," the white Daoist Xie said, then turned to depart, while Han Li watched its departing figure with slightly furrowed brows.

It was unclear whether Daoist Xie and the two corpse soul puppets were aware of exactly what had happened back, and judging from White Spirit's response, even if it did know, it wasn't going to reveal this information lightly, so he most likely wasn't going to get anything out of Daoist Xie, either.

If he wanted to uncover the truth, then he would just have to look into the matter from elsewhere.

After setting that train of thought aside, Han Li made his way to the main palace, where there were already close to thirty people present.

In addition to Daoist Xie, there were also the likes of Violet Spirit, Sha Xin, Mistress Liu Hua, Shi Chuankong, Zhuo Fa, and Xuanyuan Xing, and even Zhu Ziyuan and Zhu Ziqing were also present.

A white stone platform had been set up on one side of the palace, and on top of the platform was a circular array that was several dozen feet in size, giving off a white and golden glow.

Bursts of formidable spatial power fluctuations were emanating from the array, forming a spatial vortex that was several dozen feet in size and causing the space above it to ripple like water.

"Welcome, Fellow Daoist Han," Daoist Xie greeted as he rose to his feet, and everyone else stood up to greet him as well.

Violet Spirit was standing behind Sha Xin, and her eyes lit up slightly as she detected the vast aura exuding from Han Li.

"Sorry to keep you all waiting, everyone," Han Li said as he cupped his fist in an apologetic salute.

"Not at all, Sha Xin and the others have only just arrived as well. This teleportation array leads to the outside world, and I'll be opening it soon. If you have any matters that you want to take care of before you leave, now would be the time," Daoist Xie said as he took a subtle glance at Violet Spirit.

At the same time, he flicked a finger to send a burst of golden light flying into Han Li's body, restoring his immortal spiritual power circulation once again.

After that, he made his way over to the array, where he was immediately joined by Sha Xin, and the two of them began discussing matters related to the imminent teleportation.

Han Li was rather perplexed by this gesture from Daoist Xie, but it was naturally a good thing to have his immortal spiritual power circulation restored, and he strode over to Violet Spirit before sweeping a sleeve through the air to conjure up a soundproofing light barrier.

Before he had a chance to say anything, Violet Spirit smiled and said, "Don't get your hopes up, I'm just here to bid you farewell."

"You're going to continue to stay here?" Han Li asked as a hint of surprise flashed through his eyes, followed by a look of realization.

Daoist Xie had to have already known that Violet Spirit wanted to stay, and that was why he had restored his immortal spiritual power circulation.

"The starpower-rich environment of the Scalptia Spatial Domain is perfect for cultivating that the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts that you gave me, so I want to make some more progress before I go to the Devil Realm," Violet Spirit replied with a nod.

"That's not a bad idea. Right now, the Devil Realm isn't a very safe place, so you'll actually be safer in the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Han Li said.

"Also, I've begun cultivating the Spirit Refinement Technique as well," Violet Spirit said with a determined look in her eyes.

"I knew you would take this route," Han Li sighed in a resigned manner.

"I don't think my spiritual sense cultivation aptitude is inferior to yours. If you can cultivate the Spirit Refinement Technique, then I can as well," Violet Spirit said with a mischievous smile.

"Alright, but if any problems arise during the cultivation process, then make sure to contact me right away," Han Li said in a serious manner, and Violet Spirit nodded in response.

After that, Han Li pulled out some special items from the starpower storage ring, then placed some things inside.

"This ring isn't very good to look at, but it's a storage ring that can be used in the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Seeing as you've chosen to stay here, I'll give it to you," Han Li said as he slipped the ring off his finger before putting it on for Violet Spirit.

"I can't accept something so precious! You should keep it for yourself," Violet Spirit hurriedly replied as she began to take off the ring.

"There's no need. I'm about to leave this place, and this ring will be next to useless in the outside world," Han Li said with a smile.

"Oh, you're right, I forgot about that," Violet Spirit chuckled.

"The ring contains the full version of the Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts and a Reincarnation Palace mask. If you need to contact me for any reason, you'll be able to do so through the mask, and on top of that, there are also some other items inside, all of which should be useful to you," Han Li continued.

A film of moisture welled up in Violet Spirit's eyes as she gave a gentle nod.

"Make sure to be extra careful while I'm not by your side, and if you encounter any trouble, remember to turn to Fellow Daoist Xie for help," Han Li said.

The two of them chatted for a while longer before Han Li dispelled the soundproofing barrier, following which he turned his gaze to Shi Chuankong.

"I am eternally grateful for everything that you've done for me, Fellow Daoist Han. Just like Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit, I plan to stay in the Scalptia Spatial Domain for now, so I've also come here to bid you farewell," Shi Chuankong declared.

"You're staying here as well?" Han Li asked in a surprised manner.

"Pokong is no longer trustworthy, and I'm still very weak at the moment. As opposed to returning to the Night Sun Empire now, it's a better choice for me to stay here and cultivate. Thanks to my connection to you, I'm sure everyone will treat me well here," Shi Chuankong replied with a smile.

"Alright, then I'll be counting on you to look after Violet Spirit," Han Li said with a nod.

At the moment, Daoist Xie and the Devilish Monarch were direct enemies, so it was unclear whether Shi Chuankong was choosing to stay here of his own free will or if he had been coerced into staying.

Even though he was good friends with Shi Chuankong, he shared a closer bond with Daoist Xie, so this wasn't a matter that he wanted to pry into.

"Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit doesn't need me to look after her. Right now, she's the brightest talent in all of Puppet City, and she's the one who's been looking out for me," Shi Chuankong chuckled.

"You're Brother Han's friend, which means you're my friend, so it's only right that I look out for you. On top of that, you're a prince of the Night Sun Empire, so there's most likely going to be many things that I'll need your help with once I leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain," Violet Spirit said with a smile.

"You can count on me!" Shi Chuankong declared in a confident manner, and Han Li was quite pleased to see this.

It seemed that Violet Spirit was going to be well looked-after both in the Scalptia Spatial Domain and in the Devil Realm.

"I'm going now. Take care," Han Li said to Violet Spirit through voice transmission, and she responded in kind.

"I heard from Fellow Daoist Violet Spirit that you'll be returning to the Immortal Realm after you leave the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Come to think of it, I wasn't able to fulfill any of the promises that I made to you," Shi Chuankong sighed with an embarrassed expression.

"That's not true, you've already done more than enough by helping me find Violet Spirit. I'll just have to figure out everything else on my own," Han Li said, and Shi Chuankong's expression eased slightly upon hearing this.

"By the way, is everyone else here aside from you two also traveling to the Devil Realm?" Han Li asked through voice transmission.

"That's right. It seems like Fellow Daoist Xie has some type of plan," Violet Spirit replied, and Han Li nodded in response.

The three of them chatted for a while longer until the preparations were completed, and Daoist Xie beckoned to Han Li, who stepped onto the teleportation array along with Sha Xin and the others.

Daoist Xie was standing beside the array, and he chanted an incantation while making a hand seal, and the spatial vortex above the teleportation array instantly sped up in its revolution, quickly forming a black spatial passageway.

A burst of immense suction force surged out of the spatial passageway to encompass everyone, and Han Li took one final glance at Violet Spirit before he was sucked into the spatial passageway, vanishing out of sight.

Violet Spirit shuddered slightly as she remained staring blankly at the spot where Han Li had been standing just a moment ago.

......

All of a sudden, a ball of radiant white light appeared in the sky above a primordial forest in the Devil Realm, and it rapidly expanded to several hundred feet in size.

The space within the ball of light was churning violently, and a black spatial doorway was abruptly opened within it.

In the next instant, close to thirty figures flew out of the spatial doorway one after another.

A look of elation and relief appeared on Han Li's face as he sensed the nearby world's origin qi, and everyone else was also very pleased to have been freed from the ever-present spatial pressure of the Scalptia Spatial Domain.

Han Li took a deep breath, then released his spiritual sense in all directions to survey the surrounding area.

A few moments later, he suddenly raised an eyebrow, seemingly having discovered something.

"Fellow Daoist Han, I have some tasks assigned to me by my master, so I'll be taking my leave now. Farewell," Sha Xin said as she cupped her fist to extend a parting salute, then departed with everyone else, seemingly in quite a hurry.

Han Li watched as everyone departed for a moment, then sped away in another direction as a streak of azure light, quickly vanishing out of sight.

Chapter 996: Night Infiltration

There was a dark alley that branched off from a main street in Night Sun City.

The alley was very secluded and completely empty, and at its end was a stone wall that was riddled with pits and bumps left behind by the ravages of time.

It was nearing nighttime, and the walls of the alley were basked in an orange glow from the light of the dying sun.

Right at this moment, Han Li abruptly emerged from the wall amid a burst of spatial fluctuations.

Upon arriving in the alley, he flipped a hand over to produce a Reincarnation Palace mask before putting it on, and he instantly transformed into a young devilish man with a short horn on his glabella before making his way toward the entrance of the alley.

Not far away from the entrance of the alley was a massive tree with a lush canopy that resembled an enormous umbrella, and there were currently several people gathered under the tree, chatting with one another.

One of them, a man in black, was particularly loud, and he yelled, "That's a load of nonsense! I think the third prince would make a fine ruler. In the past, we had to go through multiple identity checks just to go to the Maha Area, but now, many of the dogmatic rules established by the first prince have been abolished, making things far more convenient."

A thin elderly man clearly didn't agree, and he countered, "That may be the case, but you have to admit that it was a lot safer to go out back when the first prince was in charge. It may be much more convenient to travel between areas now, but there have also been far more scuffles as a result. It wouldn't really matter if the trouble-makers were the only ones affected, but sometimes, their fights spill out onto the streets and ruin other people's houses."

The elderly man was holding a young boy in his arms, and the boy said in a pure and naive manner, "If only the two princes could work together..."

Everyone else burst into laughter upon hearing this.

"Pardon my intrusion, seniors, but I've only just arrived from outside the city, so I don't know where I am at the moment. May I ask where we are right now?" Han Li asked as he approached the group and cupped his fist in a salute.

"Right now, you're in the southernmost part of the Laka Area. Where are you planning to go?" the middle-aged man in black replied.

Han Li feigned a surprised expression, as if this was his first time in the city, and he exclaimed, "I'm planning to travel to the Maha Area to visit a senior of my clan, and I thought I was already almost there, but it sounds like I'm still very far away. This sure is a massive city..."

"It must be your first time here. I advise you to rent a beast-drawn carriage from the market up ahead. Otherwise, it'll take you an eternity to walk to the Maha Area," the thin elderly man said with a smile.

However, Han Li was in no hurry to leave, and he said, "I just so happened to overhear your conversation just now. Is the Holy Monarch not running the city at the moment?"

"Where on earth did you come from? I can't believe you don't know about this! The Holy Monarch went into seclusion five hundred years ago, and the third prince is in charge right now," the black-robed man chuckled in an amused manner.

"I see," Han Li replied. "Wasn't it always the first prince that oversaw the city in the Holy Monarch's stead?"

"The first prince has already been missing for over a thousand years. Some say he went into seclusion, some say he's out traveling, some say he was imprisoned by the Holy Monarch, but no one truly knows where he is," the thin elderly man replied.

Han Li nodded in response, then cupped his fist in a grateful salute before departing.

......

One night, several days later.

There was a long stretch of palaces in the northern part of the imperial city. The area was brightly lit, and teams of armorclad guards were marching back and forth on patrol duty.

Han Li had changed into a black robe, and he was racing along between the palaces, sticking to the shadows cast by the nearby walls.

At this moment, his aura was completely suppressed, and he was moving with his physical power alone, so he didn't attract any attention from the patrolling guards.

The hidden arrays in the palace walls were as clear as day to him, and he was able to easily avoid triggering them as he sped along.

It didn't take long before he reached a beautiful, standalone palace, and even before he arrived at the palace gates, he could already smell a strong medicinal aroma in the air.

All of the windows of the palace were tightly shut, and steam was rising up from the rooftop.

After briefly inspecting his surroundings, Han Li pressed a hand against the palace gates, following which a burst of silver lightning erupted out of the palm of his hand before instantly spreading over the gates, destroying all of the restrictions inside.

He slowly pushed the gates open before entering the palace, yet before he even had a chance to catch a clear glimpse of his surroundings, a gust of wind suddenly came sweeping at him from both sides.

He had already anticipated that he would be attacked upon entry, and he ducked down slightly before throwing a punch to the left and the right in unison to strike his two assailants.

The two figures were instantly sent flying back through the air before crashing into a pair of pillars with a dull thump, following which both of them slumped to the ground.

Han Li had no intention of killing them, so he had struck an important acupoint on each of their bodies, causing their devilish qi circulation to stagnate, thereby knocking them unconscious.

"If you're not here to kill anyone, then you must be here to ask for help..."

A slightly raspy voice rang out from up ahead, and Han Li cast his gaze forward to discover a pool at the center of the palace. The pool was filled with some type of viscous-looking black liquid that was slowly churning and releasing clouds of steam.

A portly figure slowly stood up from within the pool, and they were dressed in an enormous black cloak that completely concealed their head and body.

"You must be Fellow Daoist Li, right?" the figure asked.

As the portly figure emerged from the pool, waves of fiery heat surged out of their body, quickly drying their black cloak.

Han Li was rather taken aback to hear this, and he asked, "Are you the grand priest?"

"You've come all this way to find me, yet you're not even sure if I'm the person you're looking for?" the portly figure asked.

"I'm just a little surprised by how lax the security here is, so I couldn't be sure if you were truly the grand priest," Han Li said as his brows furrowed slightly.

"The security here is lax, you say? I reside in the heart of the imperial palace, and I have a pair of early-High Zenith Stage personal guards. I think you're merely underestimating your own abilities, Fellow Daoist Li," the portly man chuckled.

"I don't have much time to waste here. If you're the grand priest, then I'm sure you know why I'm here, right?" Han Li asked.

"I already knew what you wanted from me since over a thousand years ago, but I'm afraid that I can't help you," the grand priest sighed.

"In that case, I'll just have to take your head and go to see the real grand priest," Han Li said with a cold smile.

"So you still don't believe that I'm the grand priest?" the portly man sighed in a resigned manner.

"If you're truly the grand priest, then how do you know that you can't help me without even inspecting her condition first?" Han Li asked.

"I conducted some divination over this matter over a thousand years ago, and the conclusion that I drew was that this is not something I should do," the grand priest sighed.

"Not something that you should do? So it's not something that you can't do then, is that right?" Han Li asked.

"Doing something that shouldn't be done would be a grave transgression," the grand priest replied with a shake of his head.

"It's already been over a thousand years, so why don't you conduct divination over this matter again? Perhaps the outcome will be different this time," Han Li said.

The grand priest faltered slightly upon hearing this, then chuckled, "Sure, why not? But if the outcome remains the same, would you be willing to let me off the hook?"

Han Li offered no response to this.

The grand priest heaved a faint sigh, then rubbed his hands together to produce five ornate coins, following which he casually tossed them up into the air before catching them again.

The five coins fell onto the palm of his hand in a pentagonal formation, and as soon as he caught sight of them, his expression changed drastically as he exclaimed, "Who are you? How is your fate this chaotic?"

"You seem to have overstepped some boundaries and looked into something inappropriate," Han Li said in a cold voice, and nine Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords shot out of his body, slicing the surrounding space apart as they surrounded the grand priest from all directions.

A peculiar look flashed through the grand priest's eyes upon seeing this, as if he had suddenly recalled something, and he exclaimed, "Could it be that your surname is Han?"

"You leave me no choice but to kill you," Han Li said in a cold voice as his expression darkened even further.

"Surely you wouldn't strike down a fellow comrade of our Reincarnation Palace, Fellow Daoist Han," the grand priest chuckled as he extended a deathly pale hand out of his sleeve, displaying a Reincarnation Badge.

Han Li's expression changed slightly upon seeing this, but his Azure Bamboo Cloudswarm Swords were still poised to strike as he asked, "Did you find out my identity through the Reincarnation Palace?"

"That's not important. What's important is that I can now fulfill your request," the grand priest said.

Han Li swept a sleeve through the air upon hearing this, conjuring up a door of silver light that led into the Flower Branch domain.

"Is this... a legendary domain treasure?" the grand priest asked with a stunned expression.

"That's right. Please wait a moment," Han Li replied with a nod, then stepped into the bamboo pavilion through the door of silver light before carrying Weeping Soul out into the palace.

Chapter 997: Putrid Flesh

The grand priest swept a sleeve through the air, and a white jade bed slowly rose up from within the pool in the palace.

Weeping Soul was laid down onto the bed, and there was no movement in her chest, nor was there any aura emanating from her body. It was as if she was a perfectly preserved corpse.

The grand priest strode over to the bed, then lifted the hood of his cloak to reveal a set of flawless, youthful features. However, his skin was deathly pale, giving him a rather unhealthy appearance.

He examined Weeping Soul's body momentarily, following which he requested, "Please remove the puppet restrictions you've placed upon her, Fellow Daoist Han."

Han Li nodded in response before making a hand seal, and a ball of white starlight appeared over the palm of his hand before roaming over Weeping Soul's body from head to toe.

With each acupoint that the ball of light passed through, a white bone needle would break out of her skin before being plucked away by Han Li.

After all of the bone needles were collected, Weeping Soul's brows suddenly became tightly furrowed, and her entire body began to tremble violently.

At the same time, her aura was revealed, and the grand priest's expression changed drastically as he exclaimed, "What is she?"

"Don't be alarmed," Han Li reassured. "She's not a human. Instead, she's what you would call a Xing Beast."

"I see... That makes sense then..." the grand priest mused as an enlightened look appeared on his face.

"What do you mean by that?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"Xing Beasts are not a type of true spirit, but they're actually even rarer than true spirits, and they're innately born with reincarnation law powers in their bodies. I wasn't able to sense anything while that restriction was still in effect, but now that those needles have been removed, I can sense that there's a complete absence of essential power in her body. That must be why she's in her current state, right?" the grand priest asked.

"That's right. Her law powers seemed to have been stripped away during an incident many years ago, and she's been like this ever since," Han Li hurriedly confirmed.

"If I'm not mistaken, she must've been struck by reincarnation law powers during that incident, causing her own essential power to fall into a dormant state. All that needs to be done is to have reincarnation law powers injected into her dantian to awaken her essential power," the grand priest said.

"It's that simple?" Han Li asked with an incredulous expression.

"What you have to realize that reincarnation law powers are even more difficult to cultivate than the laws of space, and perhaps even more so than the laws of time. Attaining control over reincarnation law powers is even more difficult, and even the slightest mishap could result in dire consequences," the grand priest said.

"All I know is that the three paramount laws are considered to be above all other laws in the world as they reign supreme in their respective fields. As a result, they're extremely difficult to cultivate. Could it be that you're cultivating the laws of reincarnation?" Han Li asked.

"The reason why I was able to become grand priest is because I am capable of using a divination technique, and through the use of this technique, I can draw upon some reincarnation law powers to predict some future events. However, I'm still far from being able to proclaim that I've mastered the laws of reincarnation," the grand priest replied with a faint smile.

"In that case, you must be intending to use the reincarnation law powers that you can draw upon to awaken Weeping Soul's essential power, right?" Han Li asked.

"That's right. All I need to..."

All of a sudden, the grand priest's voice trailed off, and the two of them turned to Weeping Soul in unison.

She had been curled up into a ball on the jade bed, but all of a sudden, she completely relaxed and laid flat on the bed, while strands of white light began to flow out of her glabella before dissipating in all directions.

"What's going on? Why is her soul seeping out of her body?" Han Li asked in an alarmed manner.

"This is only to be expected. Without essential power to serve as an anchor, one's soul can only linger in their body for a short time before beginning to dissipate. Those needles were all that was keeping her soul locked in her body, but those needles were intended for the purpose of refining living beings into puppets, so they have a harmful effect on the soul.

Now that they've been removed, it's no surprise that her soul is dissipating at a far faster rate than before," the grand priest explained.

Han Li immediately channeled his Spirit Refinement Technique upon hearing this, and a spiritual sense threat shot out of his glabella before entering Weeping Soul's glabella, and only then did the strands of white light fade away.

"Please begin right away," Han Li implored with a solemn expression as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"I can't be interrupted during this process, so make sure to keep a lookout for me," the grand priest replied with a nod.

"Rest assured, you can count on me," Han Li vowed with a serious expression.

The grand priest didn't waste any more time as he made his way over to the end of the jade bed where Weeping Soul's head was resting, then joined his palms in front of himself as if in prayer before spreading his hands apart.

Five crimson plum blossoms flew out before dropping down onto Weeping Soul's forehead, and a series of twisted lines also appeared on the palms of his hands.

At the same time, a burst of hazy red light rose up from behind him, and his cloak began to flap around him as a burst of familiar law power fluctuations surged out of his body.

As soon as Han Li caught a glimpse of the sections of the grand priest's skin that had been revealed under the cloak, he was immediately struck by a visceral sense of disgust.

As it turned out, his entire body was riddled with massive scars and festering sores, most of which were leaking brownish-yellow pus, presenting a nauseating sight to behold.

It was clear from a glance that most of these scars were very old, and some of them had already completely sealed over to form tumor-like growths, while others were still yet to fully heal and were oozing pus incessantly.

The grand priest's body appeared to be quite rotund, but in reality, that was only due to all of the tumor-like growths that riddled his entire body.

Earlier, the grand priest had been submerged in that medicinal path, so Han Li wasn't able to smell anything aside from a strong, medicinal aroma, but he was now beginning to catch a whiff of a putrid odor from the grand priest's body.

Right at this moment, the grand priest's voice suddenly rang out in Han Li's mind.

"If the smell is too much for you to bear, then you can go and keep a lookout outside. The treatment is going to take at least two hours."

"It's fine," Han Li replied in a concise manner.

However, a short while later, Han Li's brows suddenly furrowed slightly as he said, "Looks like I will have to go outside, after all..."

"Leave everything here to me, Fellow Daoist Han. Just make sure no one gets in here," the grand priest said.

Han Li cupped his fist in a grateful salute, then appeared outside the palace in a flash.

Several streaks of light were piercing through the distant night sky, and they soon arrived no more than two hundred feet away from Han Li.

The group was led by none other than Shi Pokong, and he was accompanied by a pair of devilish men, one of which was around ten feet tall and built like a steel tower.

There was a metal visor that concealed the lower half of his face, leaving his fearsome, bloodthirsty eyes exposed.

The other figure was a benevolent-looking azure-robed elderly man, and there was a faint smile on his face as he stood with his hands clasped behind his back, looking no different from a mortal schoolteacher.

Han Li released his spiritual sense throughout the surrounding area, upon which he discovered that these three were the only ones who had come to confront him, and that there were no other powerful cultivators in hiding nearby.

The brawny man with the metal visor on his face was giving off the most pronounced aura, but his cultivation base was the lowest of the three at only the mid-High Zenith Stage. Shi Pokong was also only at the mid-High Zenith Stage, but his aura was slightly superior to that of the brawny man.

As for the elderly man, he had the most harmless appearance of the three, but his cultivation base was at the late-High Zenith Stage.

"Long time no see, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Pokong greeted with a smile as he cupped his fist in a salute.

"Indeed, Your Highness," Han Li replied with a smile of his own.

"Now that you've returned to the Holy Realm, Chuankong must be back as well, right? Where is he right now?" Shi Pokong asked.

"Are you still not willing to let him go? Fellow Daoist Shi has always cherished you as his brother, and he never had any intention of competing with you. Don't you think you've gone too far?" Han Li asked.

A hint of dejection appeared on Shi Pokong's face upon hearing this, but it quickly faded as he replied, "You're a smart man, Fellow Daoist Li, so I'm sure you're aware that there are certain things that are simply out of our control. Essentially, it doesn't really matter whether he wishes to compete with me or not."

"In any case, I do not wish to get involved in your conflict with Fellow Daoist Shi. As long as you don't interfere with my plans, I won't interfere with yours," Han Li said in an indifferent manner.

"That's fine by me, as long as you're willing to tell me what happened in the Scalptia Spatial Domain during your time there. Why is it that all of the pawns that I've planted in there have suddenly gone silent?" Shi Pokong asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Chapter 998: Agreement

"If you're so curious, then why don't you go in there and take a look for yourself? I do have to warn you, however, that the Scalptia Spatial Domain is not as safe as the Devil Realm, and you could easily meet your demise in there, just like the first prince did," Han Li sneered.

"So Zhanfeng really did die. What a pity," Shi Pokong sighed, while the two men accompanying him were both clearly very much taken aback by this revelation.

Han Li remained standing on the spot as he observed Shi Pokong in silence.

"There's no real personal vendetta between us, Fellow Daoist Li, and truth be told, I've always had a great deal of admiration for you. The situation in our Holy Realm is still quite unclear at the moment, but surely you can tell who has the better chances of coming out on top between me and Chuankong, right?" Shi Pokong said in a meaningful voice.

"I don't care about all of that. As long as you don't interrupt the grand priest here, I can let slide the fact that you tried to have both Fellow Daoist Shi and me killed in the Scalptia Spatial Domain. Once Weeping Soul is cured, I'll leave the Devil Realm right away. What do you say?" Han Li asked.

"You don't have to tell me everything that happened during your time in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, but do give me a definitive response on Chuankong's current status. Is he still alive? Has he returned to the Holy Realm?" Shi Pokong asked.

"I've already made myself very clear just now, so I suggest you don't try to push me any further," Han Li said in a cold voice, and as soon as his voice trailed off, he abruptly vanished from the spot.

In the next instant, he reappeared in front of the palace gates before stomping a foot down onto the ground.

A resounding boom rang out as a burst of shockwaves erupted forth in all directions from beneath his feet, shattering a large section of the plaza in front of the palace.

A figure came flying out of the ground with blood and dirt all over their body before frantically scurrying away into the distance.

Han Li had held back significantly in that stomp for fear of damaging the palace behind him. Otherwise, there was no way that this figure would've been able to survive.

It was a thin and wiry devilish man with black scales all over his body, and his fingers were tipped with sharp claws. It was clear he excelled in burrowing through the earth, and after scurrying several thousand feet away, he attempted to dig his way into the ground again.

However, Han Li appeared before him in the blink of an eye, then grabbed him by the throat before lifting him off his feet.

"Very impressive, you almost managed to sneak in right under my nose," Han Li sneered as he returned to Shi Pokong's trio.

All the while, the man was trembling uncontrollably as he continued to be carried by Han Li by the throat.

A dark look appeared on Shi Pokong's face upon seeing this, and the brawny man beside him roared in a furious voice, "Let him go!"

The thin elderly man's smile had also faded, and a hint of fury had surfaced in his eyes.

"Here, you can have him," Han Li replied with a smile, then casually snapped the man's neck before tossing him at the brawny man's feet.

"How dare you!" the brawny man roared as a dense cloud of devilish qi began swirling around him, and his body swelled rapidly to several hundred feet tall in the blink of an eye.

Immediately thereafter, a giant, black, octagonal warhammer appeared in his grasp, and a series of glowing crimson patterns appeared over his body, giving off bursts of peculiar energy fluctuations.

As soon as these energy fluctuations swept over Han Li, his legs instantly became incredibly heavy, as if they had been filled with lead.

The devilish giant took a step forward, shattering the ground within a radius of over a hundred feet with an almighty stomp, sending countless rocks and flying up into the air.

At the same time, he swung his warhammer down at Han Li's head, and Han Li felt as if the space above him were collapsing in layers, restricting even the surrounding space to prevent him from getting away.

Fierce killing intent was smoldering in the devilish giant's eyes, and it was clear that he had no intention of letting Han Li leave this place alive.

However, to his astonishment, Han Li suddenly took a step in his direction with ridiculous ease, as if he were taking a stroll in the park.

At the same time, clusters of specks of white light were appearing over his body beneath his clothes, and the thin elderly man's expression changed drastically as he hurriedly yelled, "Get back!"

However, it was already too late.

Han Li channeled his Heavenly Baleful Purgatory Arts as a string of dull thumps rang out from his arm, and radiant starlight erupted out of his profound acupoints to form a massive white fist projection that was launched upward with tremendous power.

As soon as the descending warhammer was struck by the fist projection, it was instantly snapped into two, and its massive head was sent flying through the air like a shooting star, quickly vanishing into the distant night sky.

However, at the same time, there was a burst of immense power that traveled up the shaft of the warhammer before twisting itself around the devilish giant's arm, climbing up his body en route to his head.

A string of grotesque crunching sounds rang out as the flesh on the devilish giant's arm was shredded into pieces, and even the exposed bone was being warped and shattered.

Right at this moment, the azure-robed elderly man sprang onto the devilish giant's body in a flash before throwing a punch into his shoulder.

His fist appeared quite frail and unremarkable, but it was imbued with astonishing power, and a thunderous boom rang out from the devilish giant's shoulder as the force of the elderly man's punch clashed against the force unleashed by Han Li's fist projection, instantly decimating the devilish giant's entire arm.

However, at the same time, the force unleashed by Han Li's fist projection was completely dispelled. Otherwise, it would've been far more than just the devilish giant's arm that was destroyed.

"Thank you, Elder Qu," the devilish giant said in a respectful manner as he reverted back to his original stature.

"There's still some residual force from that man's punch that's lingering in the wound on your shoulder. Do not attempt to regrow that arm before all of the residual force has faded. Otherwise, there will be no end to your troubles," the elderly man warned.

Meanwhile, Han Li was merely standing with his hands clasped behind his back, displaying no intention to escalate the conflict any further.

"Don't you think it's a little insolent of you to have wounded two of my subordinates here in the heart of the imperial city, Fellow Daoist Li?" Shi Pokong asked in a cold voice.

"You should be grateful to me for sparing their lives," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Looks like you've reaped some significant rewards in the Scalptia Spatial Domain, to the point that you now have the confidence to oppose our entire holy race!" Shi Pokong remarked with a cold expression.

"Don't try to intimidate me, Your Highness. I have no intention of opposing the devil race, but if you insist on forcing my hand, then I'll have no choice but to retaliate. I'm aware that there are many powerful seniors stationed in Night Sun City. For example, Elder Qu over here is certainly not to be taken lightly," Han Li said as he took a glance at the thin elderly man.

Elder Qu met his gaze, and his aura began to elevate, he was suddenly looking not so benevolent and harmless.

"But so what? I'm confident that I can at least demolish half of Night Sun City before I go down. If that were to happen, I'm sure you wouldn't be able to escape culpability. Back when the first prince was in charge, everything was so peaceful and orderly. If half of the city were to be destroyed as soon as you took his place, then I'm sure that wouldn't reflect so well on you, isn't that right?" Han Li said with a meaningful smile.

Shi Pokong's expression remained unchanged, but Han Li's words had given him pause.

If things were to play out as Han Li proclaimed, then he would undoubtedly be stripped of his duties of overseeing the city, and Shi Jingyan would undoubtedly seize the opportunity to take his place.

If that were to happen, then he would've gone to such great lengths to eliminate Shi Zhanfeng for someone else's benefit.

However, at the same time, he was rather skeptical about whether Han Li really did have the power to destroy half of the city as he proclaimed.

Right at this moment, Elder Qu's voice rang out in his mind.

"This man is a far more accomplished bodily refinement cultivator than I am. Perhap I'll be able to defeat him, but it'll be extremely difficult to kill him, and he's certainly capable of causing extensive damage to the city."

Shi Pokong was silent for a moment upon hearing this, then suddenly smiled as he said, "I was hoping to recruit you as a subordinate, but it seems like that's only a one-sided wish of mine. In that case, I won't try to force your hand any further, but please do follow through on your promise and leave the Holy Realm once Fellow Daoist Weeping Soul's condition has been treated."

"Of course. As long as I can have access to an interrealm array, I'll leave as soon as I can," Han Li replied with a smile.

Shi Pokong was naturally eager to send Han Li away, and he immediately said, "I'll return tomorrow morning to see you off in person."

"You have my thanks, Your Highness. You can go now," Han Li said with a smile, asking Shi Pokong to leave as if he were the owner of this place.

Shi Pokong's expression stiffened slightly upon hearing this, and he gritted his teeth as he departed with his subordinates.

Chapter 999: May We Never Meet Again

Han Li watched as Shi Pokong departed with his entourage, then carefully examined the nearby area with his spiritual sense, and only after confirming that there was nothing amiss did he return to the palace.

Inside the palace, Weeping Soul was curled up into a ball on her side on the jade bed, and her brows were tightly knitted with pain.

Han Li hurriedly inspected her condition with his spiritual sense, upon which a look of relief appeared on his face.

Even though she was still unconscious, her aura had already undergone a drastic change.

What was particularly worthy of note was that a wisp of essential power had appeared in her dantian, and it resembled a flame in a dark room, one that was rather frail, but instilled within the beholder a sense of warmth and comfort.

The sound of splashing water rang out from behind the jade bed, and Han Li turned to discover the grand priest slowly rising up from the pool with plumes of smoke rising up from his body alongside the acrid smell of charred flesh.

Han Li's expression changed slightly at the sight of the grand priest's face.

"Your face..."

The grand priest stroked his own face with a wry smile upon hearing this, and he sighed, "A price must be paid for using the power of reincarnation laws."

A series of charred gashes had appeared on his cheek, within which pus was flowing incessantly like molten lava, giving off a putrid odor and bursts of scorching heat.

"What about all the other wounds on your body?" Han Li asked with tightly furrowed brows.

"Every time I draw upon the power of reincarnation laws, a new wound will appear on my body, as if by an act of divine punishment. The wounds can't be healed by any means, and over time, I've been reduced to this hideous state," the grand priest explained with a wry smile.

He bent down to scoop up some water from the pool as he spoke, then splashed it onto his own face, sending a plume of white steam rising up into the air.

This was most likely one of the reasons why the grand priest had been reluctant to treat Weeping Soul.

Once this divine punishment reached a certain level of severity, the grand priest would inevitably meet his demise regardless of how lofty his cultivation base was, and judging from his current state, he had to have already been very close to reaching that point.

"I owe you a favor for this. If you have any request for me, I'll be sure to fulfill it as long as it's within my capabilities," Han Li said.

"I don't have any request for you now, but I will require your help at some point in the future," the grand priest said as he emerged from the pool.

"What will you require my help with?" Han Li asked as he raised an eyebrow.

"That's a secret," the grand priest replied with a shake of his head.

Han Li was just about to raise more questions when Weeping Soul suddenly gave a quiet groan, sounding as if she were about to awaken.

"Weeping Soul..." Han Li hurriedly called out in a gentle voice, yet she remained unconscious.

"Her essential power has been dormant for too long, and as a result, her spiritual sense has been severely taxed. If you hadn't sealed her soul within her body, she would be nothing more than an empty husk right now. Having said that, now that her essential power has returned, all she'll need is some time to rest and recuperate, and she'll eventually awaken on her own," the grand priest explained.

Han Li was feeling a little more reassured upon hearing this, and a thought suddenly occurred to him as he asked, "How are you going to answer to the third prince for helping me?"

"I was forced to help you against my will, of course. Those two can serve as proof," the grand priest replied with a smile as he gestured toward the two unconscious guards at the entrance of the palace. "If you don't think this is convincing enough, you can rough them up a little more to seal the deal."

"I don't think the third prince would be that easy to fool," Han Li replied with an amused smile.

"So what? I'm still the grand priest, so he wouldn't dare to do anything out of line. On top of that, he came here in person just now, but could only scurry away with his tail between his legs in the end, so what right does he have to criticize me?" the grand priest countered.

"That's true," Han Li replied with a nod, following which he carried Weeping Soul back into the Flower Branch domain.

The next morning, Weeping Soul still hadn't awakened, but her aura had become noticeably stronger, serving as further reassurance to Han Li. After bidding farewell to the grand priest, Han Li stepped out of the palace, and Shi Pokong was already waiting for him outside with an entourage of close to twenty people.

In addition to Elder Qu, there were three more late-High Zenith cultivators and also seven or eight early and mid-High Zenith cultivators among them.

Han Li remained composed as he chuckled, "Are you trying to scare me into submission, Your Highness?"

"Not at all, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Pokong replied with a smile. "You arrived at our Night Sun City as an esteemed guest, and now that you're leaving, I naturally had to arrange a ceremonious departure."

"That's very kind of you, Your Highness," Han Li said with a smile, then abruptly vanished from the spot, only to reappear ahead of everyone.

Shi Pokong's expression darkened slightly seeing this, and he strode over to Han Li on his own, while everyone else trailed along a short distance behind.

"Fellow Daoist Li, is it too late to say that I regret not choosing to recruit you as an ally in the past?" Shi Pokong asked.

"When you say in the past, are you referring to back when I first arrived in Night Sun City, or right before I was about to enter the Scalptia Spatial Domain?" Han Li asked with a smile.

"Is there a difference?" Shi Pokong asked.

"Not really. You could've still won me over at any point in time before giving me that Explosive Space Realm Talisman, but from the moment you made that decision, it was too late to change your mind," Han Li replied.

"That's a real pity," Shi Pokong sighed.

A look of melancholy appeared on Han Li's face as he sighed, "Did things really need to become like this between the two of you?"

Shi Pokong was naturally aware that Han Li was referring to him and Shi Chuankong, and he heaved a long sigh as a hint of dejection appeared on his face, but he offered no response.

Han Li didn't speak any further on the matter, either, and he continued onward.

The group flew to a plaza in the southern wing of the imperial palace before descending, and Han Li could see a conical pagoda up ahead.

The pagoda was riddled with a series of ring-shaped patterns that were interconnected with one another to form an extremely complex network array patterns that stretched all the way down to the ground.

The pagoda itself was no more than two thousand feet tall, and its foundation took up roughly a third of that height. A ring of transparent, rhomboid crystals were embedded into the side of the foundation, reflecting the light of the sun to give off a radiant gleam.

"Could this be the legendary Space Passage Pagoda?" Han Li asked.

"It would be impossible for you to return to the Immortal Realm using a normal teleportation array, so the only feasible option is to use the Space Passage Pagoda," Shi Pokong replied with a nod.

"Will the pagoda be able to return me directly to the Northern Glacial Immortal Region?" Han Li asked.

"Interrealm teleportation is extremely difficult to facilitate and also requires the expenditure of a vast amount of resources. Hence, we can only teleport you to the nearest point in the Immortal Realm," Shi Pokong replied.

"And where would that be?" Han Li asked.

"The Golden Origin Immortal Region," Shi Pokong replied.

"Where in the Golden Origin Immortal Region?" Han Li asked as his brows furrowed slightly.

Han Li hadn't visited that immortal region yet, but he wasn't unfamiliar with it. After all, it was home to the Nine Origins Temple and the headquarters of the Hundred Creations Mountain, and there was also a good chance that Jin Tong was currently there as well.

"That'll depend on your luck," Shi Pokong replied with a smile. "The Space Passage Pagoda can only teleport you to a random teleportation array in the Golden Origin Immortal Region."

"Alright, then let's begin," Han Li said in a direct and concise manner as he made his way into the Space Passage Pagoda, followed by Shi Pokong.

The ground inside the pagoda was riddled with array patterns, and at the very center of the pagoda were several white stone pillars with various types of strange patterns engraved upon them.

There were also transparent, rhomboid crystals embedded into the walls of the pagoda, and at the center of the white stone pillars was a platform that was around a hundred feet in diameter.

Even though the array wasn't currently operating, there were layers of rippling light surging over its surface, giving off bursts of formidable law power fluctuations.

"I hope that we never meet again in the Holy Realm, Fellow Daoist Li," Shi Pokong suddenly said.

"Rest assured, Your Highness, I'm a man of my word," Han Li replied with a smile.

"Good. Please enter the array," Shi Pokong said with a nod.

Han Li swept his spiritual sense over the array, and only after verifying that every detail of the array matched what he had been told by the grand priest the night before did he step into it.

"Rest assured, Fellow Daoist Li, this Space Passage Pagoda is extremely precious, so I wouldn't dare to tamper with it. If I somehow damage the pagoda, it'll be no less catastrophic than having half the city destroyed," Shi Pokong assured with a smile.

Han Li didn't respond, merely turning his gaze to Shi Pokong, waiting for him to activate the array.

Shi Pokong raised a hand upon seeing this, and several of the elders behind him immediately spread out around the array before sitting down with their legs crossed, making a string of hand seals to activate the pagoda.

A loud buzzing noise rang out as the entire pagoda began to tremble slightly, immediately following which a burst of silver light appeared over the platform at the center of the pagoda, while the array patterns on the ground lit up as well.

All of the rhomboid crystals embedded into the pagoda also began glowing brightly, releasing countless rays of blinding light that were too bright to directly behold.

Han Li was inundated by all of the dazzling light, and burst of formidable spatial power began to converge toward him from all directions.

Right as the array was about to be activated, Shi Pokong's voice suddenly rang out beside his ears.

"May we never meet again, Fellow Daoist Han."